(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 10)
Mr. Ha is a bit superstitious, isn't he?
I've heard a lot of celebrities
are into that.
Usually, it's the agency heads
who seek those things out.
But at my company,
they were all raised Christian,
so they can't stand it.
Are you thinking of seeing someone?
Just from time to time.
I wish my mom had gone to see one.
I sometimes think it would've been
better than therapy.
I wish there were a pill that would
let me sleep for a few years.
You don't have a care in the world,
do you?
- You do?
- I've been through my fair share...
when I was developing my game.
There was no guarantee of success.
I was getting older, and I only had a GED.
Who was your celebrity crush?
I didn't have one.
What about now?
I never said I did.
You said you "didn't," past tense.
Doesn't that mean you have one now?
You're right. I should be honest.
Of course you should.
It's you, Momo.
Oh, my.
Really?
Yes.
From what role?
I didn't fall for one of your characters.
I guess you could say I fell for you.
But you don't even really know me.
If it weren't for Ju Shin,
you wouldn't have even known I existed,
would you?
That may be true.
I heard games were everything
to you from Mr. Ha.
That's not wrong.
I bet my life on them.
Are you going to keep
dedicating your life to work?
It's not like I'm doing it all
by myself anymore,
and I'm starting to think
I want to live like other people.
But anyway, my brother has to
get married first.
That's going to be tough for Mr. Ha.
His standards are sky-high.
I'm right here.
Look no further.
What is it?
The chef wanted to know
how you enjoyed your meal.
The portions were a bit large,
but it was excellent.
- Same here.
- I'll pass that along.
You have a bigger appetite
than I expected.
I'm at the right age for it.
My late mother used to love seeing
people heartily enjoy their food.
That's such a sweet memory.
I wonder if our dinner tonight...
will become a fond memory too.
Do you have surgery tomorrow?
Pretty much every day.
Whatever you do,
don't take up horseback riding.
So many people get injured.
Seungil Shipping's youngest daughter...
She had a bad fall two years ago,
and I struggled to treat her concussion,
but she went riding again...
They say riding horses is
more addictive than meth.
Is it really that bad?
- Is that a real saying?
- Yes, it is.
Can't say the same for
cows or sheep, though.
You're surprisingly quirky and fun.
Who's texting you this late?
It's for my taxi.
- I will drive you.
- No, that's okay.
I'm not sure how to feel about that.
Are you wary of me?
Yes.
A woman has to be careful these days.
Isn't it rude to be that honest?
I don't want to impose.
How is it an imposition?
My driver's waiting.
Please don't get out.
Thank you.
Alright.
What is it?
What's wrong?
I feel dizzy.
Dizzy how?
Open your eyes.
I can't.
Open them.
What's the passcode?
It's 1103.
I've got you.
It'll pass soon.
Okay, first, I'm going to turn your head
to the left, 45 degrees.
I'm going to count to 35.
One, two, three,
four...
You'll feel better soon.
One, two, three...
Ever think about getting on
an operating table?
Lie down just once,
and I can change your life.
Go on in.
I'm sorry. It was an important call.
Of course.
Have you ever been to this house?
No.
My father never invited you over?
- No.
- Are you feeling better?
Yes.
I've barely been here
since my father passed.
I just don't find myself stopping by.
They say a house needs people living in it
to keep it from falling apart.
That rock...
is really cool and refreshing to sit on.
When I got sleepy from studying,
I'd come out here to wake myself up.
You don't like small dogs?
Maybe it's because I was small and skinny.
I'm drawn to big dogs.
But he isn't a big dog.
How am I supposed to raise a Retriever
in Yong Joong's apartment?
You can raise ten Retrievers...
in this house.
Border Collies, Jindo dogs,
Chow Chows, Tibetan Mastiffs...
You can have all the dogs you want,
and we can live here, together.
It's cliché, but I'm proposing...
over two glasses of cold water.
I'm not asking for much.
Just have my children and raise them well.
I think we're on the same wavelength...
when we talk or have any thoughts.
I can have a decent conversation...
- with just about anyone...
- I can't.
I'm selective.
Stop overthinking and complicating things.
It's not about conditions...
I'm not qualified,
and we're not a match.
What isn't?
Look, we're both on our own now.
No parents, no siblings.
So what doesn't match?
I've never even considered it.
And it's completely out of the question.
Nothing's out of the question.
Everything people do is
more or less the same.
Marriage.
They call it one of
life's most important events,
but it's just a man and a woman
living together.
What's so special about that?
Isn't it meaningful...
to stay together with hearts unchanged
and not to get a divorce?
I know what you mean.
You're not wrong,
but you never know until you try.
So you're rejecting me
without a second thought?
I'm taking that to mean
you find me completely undesirable.
It's the opposite.
You know best that,
as for qualifications,
I'm the worst possible choice.
I said let's not worry
about qualifications.
I don't know my roots.
The first humans...
Think about the first life-form.
Did it have roots?
The sky was their father
and the earth was their mother, right?
Like the digital zero and one,
life began from the combination
of yin and yang.
Are these so-called qualifications
that people came up with...
really that important?
That's all they are. Just things.
- You have a point, but...
- If I have a point, then don't argue.
You don't see me as a man?
To be honest...
Then start now.
You could at least try.
As a man, I'm flawless.
A loveless marriage?
Do you even know what love is?
Define it. What is it?
- Haven't you ever told Momo you love her?
- Leave Momo out of this.
This is about us.
I'm interested in you, Geum Ba Ra.
Since when?
This interest of yours could just fade.
Even if it does,
- let's do it.
- What are you really thinking?
Is it like, "I'm not hungry,
but the table's set."
"Even if it's not appealing,
let's just go through with it?"
- Is that what this is?
- No.
Stop questioning me.
I hate complications.
And I especially hate
having to explain myself.
If you were my patient,
I'd patiently explain everything to you.
I really can't.
Because of your background?
Or are you saying the problem is me?
It's both.
I'm sorry.
But I do appreciate...
you thinking so highly of me.
I should get going.
Is it because of Momo?
Is that what's holding you back?
That's part of the reason, yes.
We're like sisters.
It just wouldn't be right.
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't take a cab with the dog.
They'll give you a hard time.
Nurse Park should be around.
And so?
Ankle monitors are for violent criminals,
right?
I was so scared, and I was shaking.
- Do you have his number?
- What are you planning to do?
What if he holds a grudge against me?
We'll have to figure something out
without confronting him.
If he shows up again,
tell security first,
then call me right away.
Got it?
I've become such a coward lately.
I have no confidence in anything,
and I keep having memory lapses.
Lapses? How so?
I can't remember bits and pieces
of my interactions with people.
So if I ever forget something,
please try to understand.
My doctor said that could happen.
Your psychiatrist?
I was just grasping at straws.
I can't even trust myself anymore.
I'm not very emotionally stable,
and there's no way
I can get married in this state.
So...
Can't you understand?
Putting myself in your shoes, I get it.
Please eat.
I barely notice my hunger these days.
Would you like some wine?
No, that's okay.
The atmosphere here is so comfortable,
I don't need a drink.
I guess I feel at ease...
because I'm with you.
Go ahead.
To be honest,
hard liquor is more my style than wine.
Whiskey, then.
My treat. You're so busy,
but you still made time for me.
No, I'm not really looking
to get drunk tonight.
I'm just enjoying our conversation.
Since you two are friends,
I won't tell you how lonely and upset
Ju Shin made me feel.
His upbringing probably
had something to do with it.
To live up to
the late Director's expectations,
Ju Shin worked really hard.
I, at least, got to mess around
back in the day.
Just try to remember the good times.
Okay.
The way you're explaining
everything so calmly...
makes me feel a little less hurt.
It must be hard for you to get away.
I'll make time.
You can be more casual with me,
like you are with Ba Ra.
Got it.
You're not this formal with her.
He's way more down-to-earth
than Director Shin.
And I am so ready.
(Director Shin)
What? Is your phone face down?
- Yes.
- You made it home okay.
Yes.
Let me see you.
This is awkward.
What's there to be awkward about?
I've already seen your place.
Did you wash your face already?
No.
Then what?
I'm not a big fan of video calls.
It's awkward for me, too,
but the moon is just so bright.
It's a full moon.
Go take a look outside.
Okay.
You're hanging up?
Yes.
But I don't want you to.
I want to keep talking.
The driver didn't give you
a hard time, did he?
No, he was very nice.
And here I thought
my proposal was considerate.
Only to get shot down spectacularly.
I'm not a big fan of
the whole marriage process either.
It's all for show anyway.
Let's just see each other once in a while,
grab a meal, talk,
and raise a baby together like that.
You don't like that idea either?
That doesn't feel right.
You say no to everything.
Don't you want to be a mother?
To be honest, I don't think
I'd be a very good husband either.
Love is important to me, too.
Are you just going to wait around
forever for love?
I feel like we're a terrible match
and a great match at the same time.
At least, I do.
You were raised like a prince,
and emotionally, you're a bit...
A bit what?
Cold? Or maybe detached?
I'm sure it's your job, though.
Someone's told me that before.
That I can be pretty inconsiderate.
And I admit it.
You just swapped "inconsiderate"
for "emotionally detached."
What can I do? That's just how I'm wired.
As long as you're not bothering anyone,
it's fine.
Do you really think so?
- Yes.
- Then don't just think it.
Warm up to me.
I was looking at the moon,
and I thought about how you rejected me.
I wondered, "Why was I rejected?"
I just kept thinking...
I got it wrong.
I really thought you'd say yes.
You're not the type...
to play hard to get.
I'd cleared my schedule
for a week to marry Momo,
so how about we take a
walking-and-reading tour?
A trip?
Yes. Provence is a great place to walk.
The scenery is a work of art
everywhere you go.
And you're on leave from work.
I'll be the one to compromise again.
We don't have to have kids.
We can just be friends
who understand each other.
I can't possibly see you as a friend,
Director Shin.
You don't have to force it.
- As just an acquaintance then.
- Not even as an acquaintance.
Then what am I supposed to do?
- You should talk to Momo again...
- Don't mention Momo.
I've already put her out of my mind.
I've erased her.
I don't have the luxury or the reason
to dwell on bad memories.
Is it really that easy for you?
But don't you have more loving memories
than bad ones?
She lost my baby.
- She didn't on purpose...
- Let's not talk about that.
Go inside before the mosquitoes get you.
Are you worried about me?
Alright.
Make sure you look at the moon.
It's been years
since I've really looked at the moon.
Anyway,
the universe is a mysterious place.
Yes.
Do your premonitions usually come true?
The one I just had...
showed me that in the end,
you'll be by my side.
Geum Ba Ra.
(Geum Ba Ra)
Do you really think he came
just for his daughter's picture?
If he's her father, it's understandable.
Yong Joong.
You're nine years older than me.
Just for today.
It's a hard habit to break.
Anyway, if he comes back,
don't roll down your window.
Have you ever met Kim Jin Ju?
Who is it?
I'm an employee.
I'm here to drop off Mr. Ha's outfit
for tomorrow.
Right. I'm heading into the room,
so you can come out.
Okay.
You don't remember me, do you?
You gave me a ride last summer
on a rainy day.
You even gave me 100 dollars
for the taxi too.
In front of my brother's company?
- Yes.
- So you got the job?
Yes, thanks to you.
I didn't really do anything.
- Good for you.
- I'll just leave the taxi fare here.
I was so grateful that day.
Treat me to a meal instead.
I'll just leave the taxi fare here.
I was so grateful that day.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be going now.
Okay.
He had a killer body.
I knew her because
she worked for my brother.
But she looked like
a completely different person...
in that photo in the recent article.
She's gotten a lot prettier
working with me.
First, my mom passes away,
and now my stylist...
When it rains, it pours.
I really need to hold it together.
But having Ba Ra around
must be a big help, right?
She's lonely to the bone.
So being around her can really
bring you down sometimes.
Really?
Yes.
Your upbringing really makes a difference.
Can't you tell?
Not really...
Enjoy your meal.
I guess she only lets her guard down
around me.
She tends to try to be cheerful, though.
Maybe it's because
she's comfortable with me.
That doesn't sound like her.
So what did you think of Kim Jin Ju?
I'm not good at getting a read on women.
Don't you guys look at a woman's face?
I don't pay close attention
if I don't have a reason to.
So he wasn't interested in the slightest?
She once...
mentioned you to me.
- What'd she say?
- That you're considerate.
She said you even gave her money
for her taxi.
Women must be born with amazing memories.
We don't forget things that leave a mark,
either good or bad.
Should I ask Ba Ra to come out?
- Are you uncomfortable?
- No.
Three's more fun than two,
don't you think?
Should we invite her for a second round?
I might as well rub it in
right in front of her face.
The phone is turned off...
It's off.
She's always has it turned off these days.
She probably keeps getting work calls
from people who don't know she's on leave.
Let's just crash her place.
She might have gone to bed early.
- Sorry, the shoot ran late.
- What shoot?
What's next?
Are you making your acting debut now?
A magazine shoot for Choi Hoon,
so I had to be there.
Your brother is here.
Ha Yong Joong?
- Yes.
- Who's he with?
With Momo.
Momo?
The Momo?
Let's get drinks next time
for a proper cheer me up.
Okay.
Hey, James.
Mr. Ha!
I heard you two were here.
- I'm with Park Ho.
- Oh, Park Ho.
Mind if we join you?
Of course.
He's the son of the CEO
of Hanik Pharmaceuticals,
and he's a huge fan of yours.
I see...
How pathetic.
- I should probably get going.
- Why?
I'd just be in the way.
What do you mean? He's a huge fan.
He's like family to us.
He's also really well-connected.
It's good to know him.
Hey, it's been a while.
Tell me about it. Not since
you've become a huge success.
- Come on.
- You're a total icon these days.
Those are baseless rumors.
Even my twins...
What? I look a little better, don't I?
- You got the fat redistributed?
- Yes.
Momo.
Goodness, it's truly an honor.
May I have a handshake?
You're even prettier in person.
Thank you.
- Why aren't you heading home?
- Are you two dating already?
What are you talking about?
Stop dodging the question and sit down.
I was just getting some water.
I'll have ice water.
(Discovery of the Mind)
Let's just see each other once in a while,
grab a meal, talk,
and raise a baby together like that.
What do you call it if not a date?
It was just the two of you.
The same with Momo.
She just called off her engagement.
And with you, of all people.
She just sees me as an older brother.
An older brother?
But that's not you, right?
We just had a meal.
Don't read too much into it.
Not all meals are the same.
With me, it would've just been a meal.
Imagine how pathetic you'd look
if Ju Shin found out.
- It's not like we're strangers.
- That's all the more reason.
You need to keep your distance.
At the end of the day,
you're just another guy.
Smitten by a young, pretty face
and can't think straight.
Do you really want to insult
your own brother like that?
- Am I wrong?
- It's not what you say, but your tone.
If you were me, would you ignore it?
Her mom died so suddenly,
- her stylist died, she called it off...
- She was the one...
who ended the engagement.
Her stylist's dad, on an ankle monitor,
suddenly blocked her car.
How could she not be terrified?
Look, whatever the reason,
just stay away from her.
If a man and woman see each other often,
they're bound to catch feelings.
I read your article.
Your writing is very concise and good.
- You read it?
- Of course. Why wouldn't I?
You turned our short chat
into an "exclusive interview."
Ever thought about being an author?
I think you have the talent for it.
The Russian author,
Nikolay Karamzin, said that...
writing portrays the soul and the heart,
so a bad person
can never be a good writer.
Does that mean you're a bad person?
You're not.
How would you know?
- Here is our signature burger.
- Thank you.
A burger's not complete without a Cola.
I'll have one, then.
With ice?
- Yes.
- Me too, please.
You're an F, right?
And you're a T, aren't you?
I don't know. I've never taken it.
Do you want to take it now?
It's beneath my dignity.
To be defined by a test
someone else created.
You're right.
My results change every time I take it.
Do you really think you're a bad person?
I don't feel like I'm a good person.
As long as you don't feel
like a bad person, it's fine.
It means you have a conscience.
You're just being considerate.
I have no reason to be considerate.
Name one reason you think you're
a bad person.
There are too many to name just one.
Is it because of your job?
Are all reporters that slick?
Like a fox, to put it bluntly?
You don't show your true colors,
is that it?
It's always, "Director Shin."
You're polite,
but it feels like you don't trust me.
Are you an untrustworthy person?
No.
To be honest,
I'm trying not to cross any lines,
so I'm always on my toes
and keeping my guard up.
You don't seem tense at all.
Are you playing poker?
Are you saying I have a poker face?
Now I'm curious...
to see what happens
when you're not so focused...
and finally cross that line.
You might not want to see me ever again.
Go on, try me.
So you'll let it slide
no matter what I do?
I really shouldn't.
(Nikolay)
(Nikolay Karamzin)
(A Russian writer, poet,
historian, and critic)
Anyway...
Don't change your mind about this.
I didn't think Momo was like that,
but I guess her true colors are showing.
Worry about yourself.
You always understood me and had my back,
even when I dropped out.
If it were anyone else,
I wouldn't care if they dated a single mom
or some middle-aged divorcée.
What have I got to worry about?
Honestly, I've had this thought.
That you don't intend to get married
and just fake interest in women,
like you're just stringing them along.
- I sometimes think that.
- String them along? Don't be ridiculous.
You brought it up, so spit it out.
What worries me is that...
maybe you lack confidence as a man.
You mean...
that there's something wrong with me
down there?
No, I mean mentally.
Unbelievable.
Ha Yong Joong,
you're the one with the problem.
People are a product of their environment.
And I mostly work with women.
My employees, actresses, reporters,
all those society wives.
I'm telling you, it just looks like
your interest in women is superficial.
- I've been consumed by work. You know.
- And you think I haven't?
Babies are born even in wartime.
All it takes is the will.
You've never brought anyone home.
Never even introduced me to anyone.
I need to feel that forever spark.
What can I do if I haven't found her yet?
The last thing that worries me is...
that instead of women,
you like men.
Why you...
I'd have an easier time understanding
if you just said you liked Ba Ra.
Ba Ra is like a daughter to me,
if I'm being a little dramatic.
For Mom and Dad's sake,
stay on the straight and narrow.
- Mom might have understood.
- Ha Yong Joong.
I was just throwing it out there.
Don't worry.
For all our loyal listeners tuning in,
you're in for a big surprise.
That's right,
today's special guest is Momo!
Could you please say hello
to our dear listeners?
Hello. This is Jin...
(This is Jin Ju.)
I've been wanting to come on for a while.
I'm glad you finally invited me.
- It's Momo.
- Wait, weren't you already invited?
Was I misinformed?
The message never got to me...
Well, either way,
it's an honor to have you here.
Thank you.
As a game developer, have you
ever thought about that kind of problem?
Of course. I used to be addicted myself.
How old were you when you first played?
In elementary school,
my parents were strict,
so I only played for short, set times.
Was it like a whole new world?
Yes. I got really hooked in high school.
And that's ultimately why
I ended up dropping out.
That's a topic our listeners
are very curious about.
They're flooding our text line right now.
(Ryu Ju Hyun's Connect Today.)
(Is this a game or a form of gambling?)
They're almost all complaints.
When can we expect to see you
in a drama or movie again, Momo?
It might be a while...
With my mom gone,
I've lost a lot of my confidence.
As a fan, I'm sad to hear that,
but I completely understand.
A hobby might help at a time like this.
What about scuba diving?
I gave it up.
I really have to ask this next question.
Many people are sad about what happened
with you and Director Shin Ju Shin...
and are hoping you two
might get back together.
He deserves someone better than me.
Do you believe in things like fate?
How was I?
Later...
CEO Ha is on that other show.
- Really? CEO Ha?
- Yes, there he is.
- What show were you on?
- Hello.
"Ryu Ju Hyun's Connect Today."
We're heading out for dinner.
Do you have any plans?
No.
Great. Then you can join us.
Is anyone else joining you?
No. Tell the restaurant
one more person is coming.
You do radio shows too?
It was a request related to my game,
and I wanted to explain a few things.
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
Shall we go?
- Where's Pickles?
- He's at James' place.
- Did my brother call you?
- Yes.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
Not at all.
Does Yong Joong know you're here?
I didn't tell him. He's always so busy...
Was there something
you wanted to talk about?
- We're hitting rush hour traffic.
- It'll be an hour at most.
Okay, see you in a bit then.
Okay.
Why don't you just ride with us?
I drove my own car here.
You don't have any other stops to make,
do you?
No, I don't.
- Find the show CEO Ha was on.
- It might not be airing yet.
I did okay, right?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Earlier, when the DJ said
it was an honor to have you,
you should have said,
"No, the honor is all mine."
He's much older than you
and has been in broadcasting for decades.
He's a pretty big deal himself.
By any chance, have you ever heard
Yong Joong talk about Momo?
- Yes. I have.
- So you know about Yong Joong?
Yes.
I'm so worried something might happen
between them.
Why did she have to cancel the engagement?
What's your take on it?
Do you think they're a good match?
In terms of looks, yes.
No, I mean their circumstances.
She was his friend's fiancée,
which everyone knows.
"Keep chipping away,
and it's sure to fall."
What if Yong Joong makes a move
and she gives in?
Can't you do something to keep them apart?
It makes me really nervous.
I already had a firm talk with my brother,
but you never know
when it comes to men and women.
You're a really great public speaker.
So you listened to the broadcast?
- On our way here.
- We'll have the tasting course.
Yes, sir.
I couldn't stop asking myself today...
if the game I made was ruining these kids
What are you talking about?
I was flooded
with angry messages from parents.
They said their kids
were losing interest in their studies.
You can't let every single one of those
get to you.
But I'm supposed to be
a positive force in the world.
That's what my parents taught me.
They were truly wonderful people,
both of them.
If my kid were ignoring their studies
for some all-consuming game,
I'd be really upset.
But how is game addiction your fault?
I made the game.
Games themselves are fun
and a good way to relieve stress.
It's the addiction that's the problem.
Even without your game,
how many other addictive things are there?
And if you stopped making them,
would games just disappear?
People get addicted to food,
not to mention alcohol and coffee.
Do you see anyone blaming the farmers
or the coffee producers?
We need to eat to live.
The problem is eating too much.
Carb addiction, alcoholism.
It's up to everyone to use self-control.
You have nothing to feel guilty about.
She's right.
Like you said on the air today,
the game you developed
is way less violent.
Plus, it has a great story
with a clear theme of good defeating evil.
When you're done playing,
it makes you want to be a better person.
That's what I was going for.
You really felt that?
Definitely.
That makes me feel a little better.
You don't have any addictions, do you?
I'm addicted to people.
Good people.
I hope I'm one of them.
You get plenty of love as it is.
Reporter Geum.
To celebrate a successful show,
let's all have a drink tonight.
(Momo)
When were done drinking,
make sure Ba Ra gets home safe.
Got it.
You know, a man...
can have an easy life...
if he just listens to his mother,
his wife, and the woman on the GPS.
My mom passed away,
so I guess I just have to listen to my GPS
and Ba Ra.
Let's drink while it's cold.
Don't you want to hear me sing tonight?
I'd love to.
Pace yourself.
I just want to get drunk fast.
Why?
Perfect. Get drunk and duck out early.
I might as well too,
since I have both of you here tonight.
Ba Ra.
Have you ever been to karaoke with him?
I've actually never heard her sing.
You're better off not.
It's just noise pollution.
Is the chef still from Australia?
Yes.
What's wrong?
- Tell Momo to come out here.
- Okay.
Momo...
Eat your steak while it's hot.
Here you go.
- Is it organic?
- Of course.
I only feed my daughter organic steak.
This reminds me of my mom...
She always used to cut my steak for me.
She said my hands were too weak.
- Let me.
- No, it's okay.
Thank you.
Want me to cut yours?
I'm good.
You must be too happy to even eat.
Not a care in the world...
with a guy like CEO Ha watching your back.
He's not my actual brother, though.
Plenty of real brothers
are worse than strangers.
Take Manager Mimi from my salon,
for instance.
She said her older brother beat her
until she finished elementary school.
How could he hit his own sister?
I know, right?
Something's wrong with him.
(New text message)
They booked a karaoke room for us.
I already asked a friend to set one up.
Really?
Feeling any better?
Yes, a little.
If you'd gone to the ER,
you wouldn't have been seen right away.
They would've run all kinds
of tests on you,
and you'd be on medication
for over ten days.
Did you have a good dream last night?
No.
All right, sit up straight.
Slowly.
Don't shower tonight.
Just sleep as you are.
Just take off your outerwear.
You shouldn't be moving around.
I thought you only specialized
in neurosurgery.
I can even deliver a baby.
Try to find something I can't do.
Get some rest,
and be careful. It's known to relapse.
Director Shin.
Yes?
Thank you.
I mean it.
In the quiet of the evening
When the city lights grow dim
I feel the rhythm in your heartbeat
Pulling me close again
And every step we're taking
Feels like time is slowing down
So hold me in this moment
Where the world just fades away
Let the blues keep playing
Got a feeling we're dancing
With you I feel the old-time magic
Like a record softly spinning
And I'm falling
Falling all over again
Yong Joong.
Sometimes he says too much
Sometimes nothing at all
But I've seen his heart
What do you want to sing?
- I'm a horrible singer.
- That's okay. I'm a great listener.
I'm better as a backup dancer.
- Dancing?
- I won't walk away
- Through the long night
- You should be the one singing.
I'll hold your hand when it ain't right
It's love
- What gives? How rude.
- It must be an important call.
What's wrong? Are you dizzy?
(Shin Ju Shin, Director of Neurosurgery)
(Geum Ba Ra)
- Yes.
- Director Shin,
we're at Silro Hotel karaoke.
Can you come here?
- I'm on my way.
- Okay.
(Nua General Hospital)
Mr. Chairman. Good evening.
How long ago did he collapse?
It's vertigo. Director Shin's coming.
Ju Shin is?
We should call 911.
No, Director Shin
can treat her right away.
I feel nauseous.
I think I'm going to throw up.
It could be a vascular issue.
Are you dizzy?
I can't even keep my eyes open.
The same thing happened to me,
but Director Shin fixed it right away.
- When?
- Not too long ago.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why?
Because I got better right away.
Even though I'm dizzy, this feeling...
Are you sure he's coming?
The person you are calling
is on another line...
He's on the phone?
Was there any slurred speech
or signs of paralysis?
Okay.
Yes, this is he.
A stroke patient, Mr. Lee Han Jeong, 76,
will be arriving,
so get him straight to an emergency MRI.
Don't worry, Mr. Chairman.
The emergency team is on standby.
I'll be there shortly too.
Yes, sir.
- Is the karaoke bar in the basement?
- Yes, it's in the basement.
Director Shin!
Yes, Reporter Hwang, hello.
Yes, I enjoyed your latest article.
I think it's vertigo.
Hurry.
- What was she doing?
- Singing.
Call 911.
Our ENT Department is full.
I just got a call
about a critical patient.
Call 911.
That bastard.
Did he rush here thinking it was Ba Ra,
or what?
This is the Silro Hotel karaoke bar.
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
(Momo)
Only one guardian's allowed in the ER,
so you should go home.
Don't worry. She'll be fine in no time,
just like I was.
Who's coming with the patient?
(Emergency Services)
Hello?
Are you with a patient?
I just finished up.
They said there was nothing
they could do for her in the ER.
They said we have to wait
for the doctor tomorrow morning.
- They didn't do an MRI, did they?
- I heard you could fix it right away.
Ba Ra said you helped her
with her vertigo.
Yes.
So?
The circumstances were different then.
- You rushed all the way over just to...
- I told you I had a critical patient.
Is that how little you care now?
She'll feel better with some medicine.
Is Ba Ra at the hospital?
- Yes.
- Where?
Unjin Hospital?
Yes. Can't you call the ER for us?
- To the doctor on duty?
- I'd get chewed out.
Besides, there's nothing
the on-duty doctor can do.
A doctor from the ENT Department
will be there first thing in the morning.
She'll be fine as long as she lies still.
You sound so detached.
She was your fiancée, Momo.
She was even carrying my child too.
Emotionally, we're completely over.
For both of us.
Just like that?
I'll try calling Geum Ba Ra.
What took you so long to answer?
I had to step out to take the call.
I sent someone over,
so you can switch with them and go home.
There's nothing more
you can do by staying.
No, I need to be here.
She's only Momo in body.
If I were ever rushed to the ER,
would you be by my side?
Yes.
And why is that?
Like I'd ever get the chance?
The hospital staff would be
hovering over you.
So it was just lip service?
Yes.
Didn't I tell you being brutally honest
is rude and not a good look?
You thought I was serious?
Of course, I have to repay you
after everything you've done for me.
I haven't personally
done anything for you.
But thanks to you,
my vertigo was treated right away.
So it's just to repay a debt?
Does the reason matter?
The intention is what matters.
More than the reason.
I'm always grateful. I really am.
Then get rid of that feeling,
starting now.
I'm not lacking for anything,
and I'm tired of being thanked.
I don't care for effort
born from obligation.
- I'm not forcing myself.
- Regardless.
Want me to look for a purebred Retriever?
No.
What about the critical patient?
We got to them within the golden hour,
so they should be fine.
You must be exhausted.
I don't know if I'm just breaking down
now that I'm over 30.
But to be honest,
I was feeling a bit tired.
But it's gone now.
Did you see the moon that night?
Pardon?
Did you see it?
Yes, I saw it.
What do you say we talk on the phone
like this once a day?
Would you even have the time?
Don't phrase your refusal as a question.
If your hands shake when you get older
and can't operate,
switch to psychiatry.
Ever seen a psychiatrist?
No.
Then see me.
I'll be your personal doctor.
Your all-in-one personal doctor.
How about an MRI while we're at it?
That's scary. Stop trying to scare me.
Why are you afraid of so many things?
You're scared of the rain, too.
And yet you ran circles
around those detectives.
That's just because I was
too naive to know any better.
Are you a half-grown puppy now?
Even when you get older,
don't become the tiger.
Do people turn into tigers
when they get old?
My mom used to say that.
No, wait. I think I heard it from my dad.
He said women start out as puppies
but turn into tigers as they age.
You have times when your memory
isn't always perfect?
Talking to you
makes me want to see your face.
Should I come over?
Or do you want to come here?
Are you serious about coming over?
You know I don't say things I don't mean.
With your sterling character,
you can afford empty promises.
My character?
With your perfect resume,
family background, and character,
adding a spoonful of empty promises
would make you absolutely perfect.
All right. I'll work on it.
Don't you...
think I'm a pretty good catch?
Be honest.
Are you serious?
If you don't shut me down
every now and then,
do you get lockjaw?
You may be a bit cold,
but I know you're a good person.
I can just tell.
Okay. We'll end on that high note.
Okay.
Make sure you get relieved in the morning.
I will.
So coffee's not allowed either?
Probably not.
Go ask them, just to be sure.
When did they say the test was?
They said they'd let us know
30 minutes beforehand.
The red phone?
I brought it.
If you'd gone to the ER,
you wouldn't have been seen right away.
They would've run all kinds
of tests on you,
and you'd be on medication
for over ten days.
(Kim Gwang Cheol,
Jin Ju's Biological Father)
- Hello?
- This is Jin Ju's father.
Hello.
I'd like to meet with you.
- I'm sorry?
- I said I want to meet.
Okay.
(Nua General Hospital)
(The Mind)
(Director Shin)
- What are you up to?
- Reading and listening to some music.
Because you're scared of the rain?
Are you outside?
Yes.
It's raining. You should get home.
I came because it's raining.
You're here?
Yes.
You're at my apartment complex?
I feel weird about coming up.
Come down for a minute.
Or should I come up?
I came empty-handed, though.
(Jaeil Apartments)
Going down to the first floor.
What brings you here?
And you even drove yourself.
You haven't been drinking, have you?
Are you asking if I came here drunk?
No.
You get scared when it rains.
You remembered that?
A little rain like this is fine.
My gosh!
(Doctor Shin)
- Don't get too close to Ju Shin.
- Why?
You saw what happened with Momo.
But I've decided I want to get married.
- Please, don't even think about it.
- Do you have any ramyeon?
- Are you dating Ba Ra?
- We're not quite at that stage yet.
Don't lead her on.
- Are you okay?
- This is delicious.
Do you really think my Jin Ju is dead?
Did you meet with him?
- What have you all done?
- Search all you want.
Kim Gwang Cheol can run, but I can fly.
Didn't he just dump Momo for Ba Ra?
It's no contest. I like a total old man.
Why Geum Ba Ra of all people?
You want me to pull my hair back
to prove I'm Kim Jin Ju?
You want me to give you
Kim Jin Ju's face back?
If only you could make
my fantasy a reality.
Why'd you propose to Ba Ra
and make her leave?
- Leave?
- She said goodbye to me yesterday.