(All characters, places,
and organizations are fictional.)
(Children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
Really?
You'll meet her soon.
It wasn't that I was being insensitive.
It was just that instead of
a small gift like a cake,
I wanted to do something
so much better for you.
To me...
you're not a little kid anymore.
And at some point,
I started to see you in a different light.
It wasn't that I was being insensitive.
It was just that instead of
a small gift like a cake,
I wanted to do something
so much better for you.
To me,
you're truly my number one priority.
Without a doubt.
Even more than my brother.
He has plenty of close friends anyway.
And I may be exaggerating a bit,
but with no strings attached,
I want to be the one person
you can comfortably lean on...
and rely on.
I can be your big brother,
or a father figure if you need one,
emotionally.
And sometimes a friend
you can really talk to.
Anyway.
To him, I'm...
(To him, I'm...)
I've definitely become happier
since I met you.
And I feel more emotionally stable, too.
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
From now on, if there's anything
you want or need...
Don't I...
make your heart flutter at all?
Am I really just
like a little sister to you?
Go ahead and hit this clueless guy.
When I get focused on one thing,
I have a one-track mind.
Are you cold?
Let's dig in.
What do you think?
- It's good.
- Ambiance is a big part of it.
What did you have for dinner?
- A salmon salad around five.
- You must be starving, then.
No.
Why the short answers all of a sudden?
I'm busy eating.
You're so cute.
- Only for you.
- You'd better be.
Seeing you, I get why dads dote
on their daughters.
You'll meet a good guy
and get married someday.
But it'll be hard to find one
as great as me.
Where's all this confidence coming from?
Other than my education,
I'm pretty much the whole package, right?
Shoot, I forgot the water again.
- I'm not thirsty.
- You'll get an upset stomach.
If you could just be mine
and stay by my side,
I thought I could live on...
without ever seeing my mom and dad again.
(Ba Ra)
(Geum Ba Ra)
(Save)
So you don't even like
Shine Muscat grapes?
Yes. It's not tangy or anything.
It's just sweet.
If I were a flavor, what would I be?
Sweet? Tangy?
Unripe.
Compare me to an animal, then.
The lord of all creation.
No animal comes to mind.
You don't have to be nice.
I'm serious.
I just take and take
from you, shamelessly.
I want to give something back,
but you already have everything.
That's how love works.
It flows downward, not up.
But plenty of children are devoted
to their parents.
I guess I should have kids, right?
That's the one thing I envy Ju Shin for.
I'm so envious of Momo.
The wind is chilly.
It's still warm under the sand.
We came for a sand bath, remember?
Don't you want to?
We can wash up at the hotel.
They sell golf wear in the lobby.
Isn't it warm?
It's fine.
How does it feel?
It's a strange feeling.
But not in a bad way.
You can really see the stars out here,
can't you?
Yes.
This is better than doing it
in the blazing sun.
Who used to bury you in the sand?
Your mom?
My brother.
He has such a great personality.
I'm sure he has his own pain, deep down.
But he never shows it. Not at all.
You should try to have a deep talk
with him sometime.
I've tried asking him,
and he just said he's grateful
to be part of our family.
End of story.
You know how guys are bad
at expressing themselves.
Me too. I'm so glad I met you.
The feeling's mutual.
I was always jealous of my friends
who had little sisters.
This is weird.
I'm getting sleepy.
You're probably just tired.
You drove for hours and even took a plane.
You're not going to disappear
when I wake up, are you?
Maybe.
Give me your hand.
How do you like a sand bath
under the moonlight?
The one person who creates
these memories for me...
is you.
All your difficult memories...
will be buried under good ones.
I'll make sure of it.
They don't make them like me anymore.
That's true.
You're really one of a kind.
I'm going to poke you in your side
from now on.
But I'm really ticklish.
I'm not good at expressing myself either.
Because I grew up in the orphange,
I can't help
but be a bit emotionally withdrawn.
I admit it.
I don't see that at all.
I just think you're cute.
And adorable.
Aren't you curious about
what my name means?
A lot of people ask me.
You said it's "Jung Yoong" in reverse.
- When did I tell you that?
- I heard it from An Hee.
You must've heard that
when you were little. You remember?
- Yes.
- Smarty-pants.
He didn't talk trash about me, did he?
Of course he did.
So that's where
all my cringey stories came from.
He said you were the most loyal person,
and that Ha Yong Joong
was an incredible guy.
When it comes to loyalty,
An Hee's the real deal.
I was so busy developing my game...
that I couldn't find you sooner.
Yong Joong,
did you ever believe that when people die,
they become a star?
No.
I have to take care of my kiddo
for An Hee's sake too.
Look for the Big Dipper.
Okay.
There it is.
I wish I could fall asleep
just like this and never wake up.
All my hope is completely gone.
I wanted a baby more than anything.
A beautiful baby that looks just like you,
not anyone else.
I have nothing to live for now.
Just thinking of you...
was enough to get me through anything.
We're not even blood-related.
Is that all I am to you?
Just a little sister?
If I were to disappear from this world,
I wonder if you'd think of me
as a woman then?
Not as that little girl with the bob cut,
but as the woman I am now.
You'd remember me like that, right?
I'm not really doing the world any good.
Is there any reason for me to keep living?
- Hey.
- You're up?
Yes.
I need you to come over.
Are you not feeling well?
No, but still.
I'm out of town,
so it'll take three or four hours.
A business trip on the weekend?
No, I'll explain when I get there.
Okay.
Can I say we came together?
Of course.
It's not because of some bad press, is it?
Look it up.
Set up a meeting with CEO Ha Yong Joong.
Tonight will work too.
Why?
You should be there too.
Momo asked for a meeting with you,
but she wouldn't say why.
How about lunch tomorrow?
My brother is supposed to
come over tomorrow.
A real gift.
Was that a gift?
You don't usually wear accessories.
He brought it back for me from Japan.
You didn't order wine.
You can't be drinking.
I'm going to drink.
Is something wrong
between you and Director Shin?
- Is there anything you need?
- I'll do the wine pairing.
- Yes. We offer 4 and 5-glass options.
- Six glasses.
Of course.
Please be my big brother,
like a real big brother.
He hit me.
Director Shin did?
He thinks he can treat me this way
because I have no one left.
Why? What happened?
I had a miscarriage,
and he accused me of getting
an abortion on purpose.
You had a miscarriage?
Seriously? Ju Shin?
He's gone completely insane.
Where did he hit you?
My face.
My cheek...
But Director Shin is usually
so level-headed.
There are things you just don't lie about.
Why would I make this up?
Are you okay?
Shouldn't you be in the hospital?
I've recovered now.
But it's the emotional pain
I'll never forget.
They say you shouldn't even
hit someone with a flower.
I've never been hit before,
not even for an acting role.
What about in "A Maiden's Prayer"?
You think they hit for real?
It's all show.
I think I'm going to call off
the engagement.
- That's ridiculous.
- Why is it ridiculous?
Most engaged couples fight a few times.
It wasn't a verbal argument.
I'm telling you, he hit me.
He apologized, right?
A single, insincere word.
I think it's better to end things now
than to get married and divorce later.
Don't say that.
There's no one like him.
In what way?
- He's perfect in every...
- You try getting hit.
You know what that's like,
the humiliation.
I heard you got beaten up a lot in school.
When did I ever say that?
Did you hear that from Kim Jin Ju?
Does that matter?
You should also try to see it
from Ju Shin's point of view.
And what's his point of view?
Since men can't just decide
to have a child,
when it comes to their own bloodline...
I wouldn't call it an obsession, exactly,
but I'm sure
his expectations were very high.
He's probably just blaming himself inside.
I wish you wouldn't defend him
just because he's your friend.
I've completely lost
all my feelings for him.
Please, you're like a brother to me.
Help me.
Are you really thinking of
calling off the engagement?
I'm just an outsider.
If I get involved, it could backfire.
And Ju Shin is an incredibly proud man.
That's exactly why
I decided to end things.
Who doesn't have pride?
Is he the only one who gets to be proud?
And I'm Momo!
Yong Joong.
All this time,
I've actually been jealous of her
at times.
I have no one left now.
What did you think
when you first met Momo?
She was even prettier in person, right?
You think men only care
about a pretty face?
They don't?
I don't...
Did Momo tell you
her first impression of me?
- Yes.
- What did she say?
I know she wasn't impressed.
Not "unimpressed."
She saw it as just a courtesy meeting.
She only went because of James.
I was drawn to her unique vibe.
First, I fell for
her insane acting skills.
Me too.
She has this innocent audacity.
How should I put it?
She's wise beyond her years.
How is Momo...
now?
Lately.
If I were your real sister,
what would you do in this situation?
Would you just push me
to go through with the marriage?
It's something you have to address
and move past.
I really can't get married like this.
(James)
It's my brother. I should take this.
- Hey, James.
- Get over here, quick!
- What's wrong?
- What am I going to do?
- Something happened.
- Go on, you should check on him.
We'll talk later...
Why aren't you saying anything?
You got hit once.
But Director Shin lost his child.
He hit me because I miscarried.
I told you that you shouldn't be swimming.
From his perspective, it's understandable
that he would be angry.
Are you in love with him?
Why are you so quick to defend him?
How can you even say that?
What about you? I said he hit me.
You think it's because I went swimming,
just like he said?
Shouldn't you feel for me and be worried,
like Yong Joong is?
- I'm sorry, that's not what I meant...
- Forget it.
- I was so excited to be an aunt...
- I said forget it.
Ever since CEO Hyun passed away...
Since then?
She's been a little...
on edge, I guess?
Once she gets married and has a baby,
she'll be our lovely Momo again.
Lovely Momo?
Do you have a nickname?
- Me?
- Yes.
- No.
- Not even as a kid?
At the orphanage, they called me a crybaby
because I cried a lot.
What about now?
- Almost never...
- No reason to cry?
Or did you get tough?
Your tenderloin steak.
By any chance,
do you remember Ji An Hee?
- From high school.
- Of course I remember him.
Everyone at school knew who he was.
He was the top dog.
I heard he died, right?
Yes.
He's the reason
I stopped crying all the time.
I guess he was good for something.
Yong Joong...
didn't go to college because he lost
interest in studying, thanks to Ji An Hee.
But it all worked out for the best
in the end for him.
He could've done even better.
A college degree doesn't mean
that much these days.
If it's so meaningless, why did you go?
I started with nothing.
When you have nothing,
you at least need an education.
Do you really want a brother?
Of course.
- I don't have any ulterior motives.
- I wasn't asking if you had any.
Are you feeling insecure?
Worried he'll give me more attention?
Think whatever you want.
She must be so insecure.
What's she going do if I latch onto him?
An endorphin rush.
I don't think we should call the police.
It'll just cause problems.
Exactly.
What if it hits the news sites right away?
Both of the watches?
The Bvlgari bracelet and Milano pouch...
I really treasured those.
You should put your valuables
in a safe deposit box...
and just move back in
to the Cheongdam villa.
I told you,
I'm not meant to live in a nice place.
What kind of superstition is that?
You still got robbed living here.
It's better than losing my health.
Then think of it as getting your bad luck
out of the way by losing your things.
It's true what they say.
Ten guards can't stop one thief.
Do you have a lot of friends from college?
A fair amount.
No real close friends, though.
That's probably because
you don't open up first.
How did you know?
- You just seem that way.
- It's the other way around.
They act friendly to my face,
but they are the ones
keeping their distance.
It could just be your own insecurities.
I'm...
not senseless.
Sounds like Kim Jin Ju
was your only best friend.
You must miss her.
Have you forgotten her already?
How could I ever forget her?
It still doesn't feel real.
She wasn't the type
to give up on life that easily.
There are two types of people.
There's a type who, when a loved one dies,
blames themself for what they did wrong.
And the type who only recalls good things
and gets trapped in their grief.
Which one are you?
I wouldn't say...
I miss her all that much.
Sounds like you have some hard feelings.
Everyone has different sides to them.
So she had a lot of faults?
Is that what it sounded like?
Yes.
What about you?
Your parents...
As for me,
I don't have any guilt.
I don't think I ever disappointed them.
At least, that's what I think.
Kim Jin Ju really liked you.
All the kids at the home did,
but she especially liked you.
Never mind people.
What do women like?
What are they into?
So many things.
What about you, Geum Ba Ra?
I deliberately tried
not to think about it.
I hate the feeling
of wanting things I can't have.
That's kind of sad.
Think about it, and if there's anything
you want, let me know.
You even made time for me
when you were busy.
It was the least I could do.
That's beside the point.
You're always taking me
to nice places like this.
But you treated me to a meal last time.
You might think less of me for this,
but to be honest,
I'm not really used to being
on the receiving end.
As you said, it might be a bit
of an inferiority complex.
Do you know the difference
between a bribe and charity?
A bribe is given for a specific purpose,
- while charity is just given.
- Right.
A veteran congressman,
who'd received a lot of funds,
was once asked a question.
"How do you take money
without any repercussions?"
And the veteran congressman replied,
"You have to debone it carefully
so you don't choke."
When they asked how to debone it,
he said that was his secret.
"You just have to eat boneless whale meat.
The whale is the conglomerate."
Besides whales,
what other fish is boneless?
- An octopus?
- Exactly.
The octopus is money from a faction boss.
And aren't I basically your faction boss?
So you can get used to
accepting things from me.
I'll think about it.
You should smile more often.
You too, Director.
I'm a man.
What's gender got to do with smiling?
It makes me look frivolous.
Are you strong? Or just pretending?
I told you to smile, not to be cheeky.
Is it cheeky to ask a question
I'm curious about?
You're curious about me?
You want to know more about me?
No.
Is that your pride talking?
A lack of interest?
It's just that...
you're someone
who grew up with a lot of love,
but you seem so rigid.
Did you hear about Momo's dream?
- A conception dream.
- No.
She said a giant yellow serpent
bit her on the shoulder.
It must be a boy.
My mother also had a dream
about a serpent before I was born.
My sincerest congratulations.
I turn someone lower than dirt
into a Cinderella,
and she can't even properly
carry one child.
I have no one left now.
Right now?
I'm out playing golf.
And you feel like playing golf?
You're the one who said I should learn.
Right, you listen so well,
but go and swim your guts out...
People change their tune
when they get what they want...
You're not happy with me, are you?
You regret operating on me, don't you?
What do you want me to say?
I want to do whatever you want.
Let's have another baby, then.
What's today's date?
Let's just call off the engagement
and end it.
I refuse to live my life being abused.
I'm beneath you, Director.
I'm just Momo on the outside.
I'm flawed and lacking...
Are you serious?
I think I'll get tired of
walking on eggshells around you.
In fact, I'm already exhausted.
How long has it even been
for you to feel that way...
I'll keep your secret.
I'll take it to my grave.
So what's your plan?
I'll just keep living as Momo, I guess.
Just don't act.
Just shoot whatever commercials
come your way.
I won't. Acting isn't for just anyone.
You won't regret it?
- What more is there to lose?
- Lose?
- You have it all.
- I even gave up my own body.
I'll have Geum Ba Ra release the story.
Excited at the thought of
having the world at your feet?
I told you, I'll live quietly.
I won't cause you any trouble.
Yes, a little more toward the camera.
Momo, a bigger smile, okay?
Yes.
That's great.
You're starting to loosen up.
Yes, look at the camera more.
Okay.
To Kim Jin Ju, Director Shin is
a deity or her Prince Charming.
- Now, I...
- We're good.
Momo is pretty. I'll give her that.
We're rolling.
Are we working through dinner?
I sat in on the meeting
with Ba Ra and Momo last weekend.
I know you must've been
frustrated and upset,
but still, did you have to
hit her in the face?
That's enough.
Haven't you heard
we're ending the engagement?
We're going to.
It was her idea.
You two were crazy about each other.
I know you don't really show
your feelings much, but...
People's feelings really do change.
They're bound to.
You know how James
can't even take care of himself...
and calls himself a relationship expert?
He says when a woman wants to break up,
it's actually a plea for more attention,
more care, and more love.
Forcing yourself to feel something
isn't love.
Okay.
Yes, look right into the camera. More!
I'm so hot.
If I hold out my hand, who could resist?
They'd be tripping over themselves
with gratitude.
Ha Yong Joong is actually kind of great.
Do you ever think about your first love?
I don't have a first love
worth remembering.
You dated a lot in high school.
Only two of them were serious.
My first love...
was Ba Ra.
She was just a little kid,
but I could never forget her.
She'd pop into my head now and then.
And then that little kid appeared,
all grown into a lady.
She's just a kid to me.
First impressions are everything.
She was so young and small...
that I thought she was a 5 or 6-year-old
kindergartener.
If you say so.
Is it really over for good?
You'll probably see her now and then.
Doesn't look like it.
It'll just make for some messy headlines,
that's all.
Was it that easy to just call it quits?
Can I come with you to Yong Joong's place?
Why?
Now?
I suddenly really miss Pickles.
I'll take you.
You sure Yong Joong won't mind?
He's not home yet.
Is he seeing anyone?
No. Not that I know of.
I can't believe he's single.
He's such a catch.
Run the story. "Momo and Shin Ju Shin
End Their Engagement."
(Exclusive: Momo and Director Shin Ju Shin
End Engagement)
Goodness, look at you,
landing an exclusive on your last day.
Take the year off,
but you have to come back.
So what caused the split?
- They didn't really have a fight.
- You can't be serious.
Just as it says in the article,
they couldn't get married happily...
after all they've been through.
So they decided to call it off.
Who made the final call?
It was mutual.
It's like how you can just sense...
that the feelings aren't
what they used to be.
I bet it was Shin Ju Shin
who started to lose interest.
- You heard something?
- A distant relative of mine...
apparently went to the same college
and was in the same major as Momo's mom.
But she apparently got pregnant
her freshman year and dropped out.
Then one day, she pops up on TV
as Momo's mother.
So she really is a college dropout.
So she got married young?
If she'd had the baby from back then,
they say the kid would be much older...
- than Momo.
- So what's the story?
It means she has a past.
Shin Ju Shin comes
from a prestigious family of doctors,
but Momo's pedigree
doesn't really measure up.
What's wrong with Momo's background?
She's the only daughter of Sun Gallery.
- Momo's mom is his second wife.
- Really?
His first wife died soon
after their wedding.
They had no children.
It's not public knowledge.
I got curious and looked it up
while on the art beat.
There's a huge age gap, too.
Something like 16 years.
- Almost 20 years, actually.
- My gosh.
So what happened to the baby?
Doesn't that mean Momo has a half-sister?
No, it means same mother,
different father.
She might not have had the baby.
You two are close.
Has she ever mentioned a big sister?
- No.
- Why would she?
She might not even know.
That makes sense.
I wouldn't bring it up either
if I were her.
Where's Pickles?
At Reporter Geum's place?
No, Momo's watching him for a while.
That's what I came to talk about.
So, what are you going to do about it?
- About what?
- You know what I mean.
Now that they've
called off the engagement...
I can't exactly ask either of them.
Aren't you the one who caused it?
No, I'm not.
You're tempted, aren't you?
What? There's nothing to be tempted by.
You don't sound so sure.
Momo is absolutely off-limits.
I hate to even bring this up,
but Ju Shin even got Momo pregnant.
An OB-GYN I know told me in confidence.
Was the doctor a woman?
What does their gender matter?
Don't change the subject.
You have a real knack for making things up
and jumping to conclusions.
You think I'm making this up?
Can't you answer me?
I haven't even thought
about something like that.
Don't start now.
And don't you dare change your mind.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Your hunches are never right.
Please.
It's all up to you.
We've got to go for round two, right?
Of course!
You're the guest of honor! Don't leave.
I won't.
Come on, none of us has ever heard
Geum Ba Ra sing.
That's right.
You're better off not hearing me sing.
We'll be the judge of
whether it's noise or music.
- I think I'll just stick to my day job.
- Backup dancing?
Right.
I'm the real, real deal
Totally the real deal
(Century's Love... Century's Breakup?)
(Momo loses fiance
after losing her mother)
(Exclusive: Momo and Director Shin Ju Shin
End Engagement)
Do you think your daddy will
call tomorrow?
He will, right?
Want some? You thirsty?
I'm Lucky, and you're Lucky, too.
I'm not Momo.
I'm Jin Ju. Kim Jin Ju.
When did you get here?
You should've just come in
or rung the doorbell.
I've been drinking.
Good for you.
A lot...
Feeling rough? Nauseous?
I don't know.
I feel awful.
Ice water, iced coffee, or honey water?
Sorry.
I'll get out of your hair in a bit.
- Go on your run.
- I can skip a day.
The pharmacy probably isn't open yet.
It's not that bad. I'm okay.
Is something wrong?
A work dinner.
It was for my leave.
For now, just get some rest.
If I didn't have work,
we could've gone somewhere for a few days.
- Who's "we?"
- You and me, of course.
That would be so nice.
How about we go to Japan next month?
But you've already been to Japan.
You haven't been to China, have you?
Everything's going your way.
I'm so jealous.
Have you talked to Momo?
No.
I wonder how Momo's feeling.
She asked me to be
like an older brother to her.
It's like I'm gaining a new little sister.
A "little sister"...
But you like her as a woman.
I wouldn't go that far.
You want to be in love with her,
don't you?
Like, true love.
One-sided feelings aren't true love.
My little rascal comes first.
Momo comes second.
What if Momo starts to like you back?
What if she falls for you?
I'm Ju Shin's best friend.
That doesn't cross my mind.
But you wouldn't have a reason
to turn her down, right?
I don't think I could handle
seeing you two together.
I'll leave.
There you go again,
saying such hurtful things.
Where would you go?
You think I wouldn't be able to find you?
Always pulling these little stunts.
Honestly, you big baby.
How long are you going to see me as a kid?
Forever.
You by my side, and me by yours...
We're going to grow old together.
So stop with these spiteful thoughts.
Momo has been so prickly with me lately.
She's not the same Momo I used to know.
Try to understand her.
Anyone else would've had
a breakdown by now.
Until she's had time to heal,
be the big sister she can lean on.
I'm only human and a woman.
Don't I need someone to lean on?
You have me.
For one month...
No, even for just one day,
I wish I could be your girlfriend.
Next time you go drinking, call me.
I'll come pick you up.
As if you have the time.
I'd send my driver at least.
I'll make you some hangover soup.
- I'm going to sleep.
- Get some sleep first.
I'll bring you something to wear,
so go wash up.
You all right?
- Yes.
- You're not dizzy?
No.
Careful now. Don't fall.
Hey.
Yes?
What is it?
There's a new toothbrush in the cabinet.
Are you feeling sick?
No.
Can you feel...
the way I like you...
and love you?
Sometimes, I can't.
But right now, I'm starting to.
Sometimes...
Sometimes what?
Tell me.
I feel like you don't really know
how I feel.
That's my line.
If that's how you really felt,
then I'm sorry.
It's because I grew up with my brother.
Honestly...
Speak of the devil.
I left some clothes out for you.
Hey, James.
Last night I dreamed Oiji showed up,
but almost all of its fur had fallen out.
You're still thinking about Oiji?
Of course I am. When have I ever stopped?
I think I should have
a memorial rite performed.
Don't go overboard. It wasn't a person.
You know how much Oiji meant to me.
Not more than you, of course.
Then just do it.
You know a monk, don't you?
You mean you're going to do it
at a temple?
People will say
you're disrespecting Buddhism.
Buddhism teaches compassion
for mute animals, especially dogs.
Whatever. You figure it out.
I can't ask them to do that.
- Oiji meant a lot to you too...
- I have to go for my workout.
Hello?
- It's good karma.
- Then you can build enough for us both.
Hello?
Darn it.
Oh, Oiji.
Is there anything I wouldn't do for you?
What brings you here at the crack of dawn?
(Momo)
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Charges may apply...
(Momo)
The phone is turned off.
Why is her phone off?
Who does she think she is?
Don't you dare pee anywhere you want.
You'll get a spanking.
Hello?
Momo?
Yes.
I almost didn't answer
because it's an unknown number.
I've been getting flooded
with calls and texts.
So I turned off my main phone.
I see.
Is something wrong with Ba Ra?
She's never turned her phone off before.
She's sleeping.
She said she drank a lot
at a work dinner last night.
At your place?
Yes.
She'll call when she wakes up.
Okay. Don't tell me they
took things to the next level.
Things must be tough.
I heard from Ju Shin.
You can buy me a drink
to cheer me up sometime.
Sure.
Can I keep Pickles for a few more days?
Of course.
He helps take my mind off things.
I'm glad to hear that.
If you start having bad thoughts,
think of a good memory or listen to music.
Okay.
Should I save this number?
Yes.
Talk to you later.
Okay.
Grandfather says she died
and came back to life.
- After she died?
- Yes.
You should be worrying about yourself.
You need to have a major ritual performed.
There's a woman clinging to your shoulder.
A woman?
How old?
She died before her time.
What are we to do
with all that resentment?
What did you think of the visit today?
The way I feel now,
I think I should visit more often.
Now that you've set your mind to it,
you might actually go once
for every three times you say you will.
If you'd come with me,
I'd go three times instead of two.
Or even four.
I'll accompany you every time you go.
Don't make empty promises.
Not just anyone can afford
to make empty promises.
- Who, then?
- Someone who can afford to?
You always seem so busy and rushed.
Sometimes I wonder...
if I had a lot of bad karma
in a past life.
- Karma, is that what you call it?
- Yes.
Maybe I was so lazy back then...
that I don't even have
a moment to breathe now?
If I'm being a little dramatic.
- Here is the ribeye cap.
- Thank you.
What kind of hope did you have
at the orphanage?
They say there are no hopeless situations,
only people who have given up hope.
Who said that?
Shimon Peres,
the former president of Israel.
When I couldn't find any hope,
I'd use my imagination.
Almost all the kids...
spend a lot of time imagining
their parents coming for them.
But I've had my reality check,
so I don't have those dreams anymore.
But you often see stories about
families reuniting after decades.
That's almost always for kids
who went missing or were lost.
If I were the one who'd abandoned
my own child,
I couldn't bring myself to look
for them out of guilt.
Do all reporters read a lot of books?
I think the senior editors read a ton.
I just pile them up,
but never get around to reading them.
In college, I was too busy working
part-time jobs to read as much as I liked.
What kind of part-time jobs did you have?
All sorts of things.
Being an event guide paid pretty well.
Do you know who the poorest king
in the world is?
The one on minimum "wage."
Do you have any life goals
left to achieve?
I've achieved them all. So far.
Oh, really? Already?
You're incredible.
Have you ever read a book
called "Laughter"?
I don't think so.
It says in your 20s,
you take pride in being able to love,
and in your 30s,
you take pride in having a lot of money.
What about your military service?
Exempt. I have flat feet
and am the only son for four generations
My dad served in the Vietnam Ski Unit.
Oh, okay.
What do you mean?
There's no such thing
as a ski unit in Vietnam.
It's a tropical country.
Oh, right.
So you have a clueless side to you.
Actually, I'm pretty much a mess,
except when it comes to work.
A little imperfection
helps you live longer.
But you don't have any, do you?
I guess I'm destined to die young, then.
Director Shin.
Parents have an obligation
to live a long life.
Momo is carrying your baby.
I see your teeth are fine, though.
I heard neurosurgeons
get cracked molars...
from clenching their teeth during surgery.
It's too early in my career for that.
I heard something too.
That it's tough for new reporters, right?
It's incredibly tough.
Speaking from experience?
I'd rather not say.
But I asked.
What could you have to hide from me?
It's not my own story, but...
To be honest,
you're the one I find most intimidating.
Well, don't be.
You can be comfortable with me.
It's not that I don't trust you,
Director Shin.
You can be comfortable with me.
When we're on the police station beat,
seniors teach us to hold our own.
They tell us not to let the detectives
push us around.
One time, a son of some big-shot CEO
got busted for drugs,
and he was being interrogated
in the Chief's office.
You wrap your phone in a plastic bag
and take it in with you.
It's that intense?
You're in huge trouble
if you don't answer your seniors' calls.
And if you get a scoop?
You get a "good job."
What about the exclusive interview
you got with me?
That was a huge scoop.
I'll never forget it.
Just remembering it isn't enough.
(Messages)
He might want to get rid of me,
but he can't just take out the brain.
To get rid of me, he'd have to kill Momo.
Could he kill Momo and get away with it?
Where should I go and have brunch today?
If she finds out it's me and not Momo,
I wonder how much
Geum Ba Ra will freak out.
Who would've thought
I'd get to enjoy a life like this?
An orphan like Kim Jin Ju.
What if I put Ba Ra's brain in your head?
No, wait. In Ba Ra's head...
What if I put your brain in there?
Woof, woof.
Just remembering it isn't enough.
Please tell me what it is you want.
Momo...
is seriously lacking in refinement
and general knowledge.
(Humanities for Self-discovery)
Recommend some books or something
for her to read.
Do you know a good English tutor?
Or you could just teach her yourself.
(Do you know who the poorest king
in the world is?)
(The one on minimum "wage.")
Today, it's strawberry cake.
Geum Ba Ra.
Can I see you right now?
Where?
I'll text you the address.
I can't bring Pickles, can I?
- Why?
- I'm at Momo's, and he's all alone.
Bring him.
Can't I come too?
I'm curious to see
how Yong Joong lives on his own,
and we were going
to see each other again anyway.
I'll ask him.
Hello. I'm Jin Ju's dad.
Kim Jin Ju.
- Yes?
- Is there a bench nearby to talk?
It'll only take a minute.
What is it?
Roll down the window a bit.
You have pictures of my daughter,
don't you?
You must have some, don't you?
What's your number?
Send them to me, please.
I need to at least look
at her picture to get by.
I don't really like taking pictures.
Who doesn't?
Me.
So, because you don't like taking them,
you're saying you don't have any?
That's right.
But how could you
have never taken a single picture?
You haven't even looked for one.
I don't have any.
I get so sick of it
that I rarely take personal photos.
But my daughter was your stylist
for over three years, wasn't she?
I suppose so.
I deleted the few I had.
Pickles!
(Calls: Ba Ra)
Why'd you take him without telling me?
You didn't even wait for me.
(CEO Ha Yong Joong)
What the...?
(Humanities for Self-discovery,
Humanities Mindset)
(Momo)
The person you're calling is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
(Momo)
- Hello?
- I'm sorry.
I was saving your number
and accidentally called.
I see.
Okay, bye.
You sound a little down.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine.
Okay.
Can I see you?
Sure. Are you home?
- Yes.
- I'll head over now.
Plan B isn't too far from you, right?
Right.
It's rush hour,
so it might take me 40 to 50 minutes.
The map says we're here.
I'll get out here.
- It's raining.
- The sound woke me up.
Gosh, it's really coming down.
So much for the weather forecast.
Call someone to come out and get us.
If it wasn't for work, I'd be home
making some savory pancakes right now.
Still, I got a huge thing
out of the way today.
- You heading home?
- Yes.
Hello, sir.
She's one of Hanjun's assistants.
Right.
Get in.
He's my brother, James.
Thank you.
If you could just drop me off
in the alley by Hakdong Intersection...
- Are you two related?
- He's my older brother.
- But the age gap...
- Yes, it's pretty big.
Are you a stylist?
Just an assistant for now.
This rain came out of nowhere...
Which actor's styling team are you on?
- Hanjun's.
- I hear assistants only get an allowance.
Yes. I just graduated this year.
I heard my brother is hiring next month.
Really?
You should apply.
I'll work really hard, so if you could
put in a good word...
The car died.
- What?
- Hey, there's a taxi! Hurry!
- Thank you so much.
- Wait!
This is for the cab fare.
Quick, before someone else gets it.
(Doctor Shin)
Have you ever met Kim Jin Ju?
He had a killer body.
I wonder if our dinner tonight
will become a fond memory too.
He's way more down-to-earth
than Director Shin.
And I am so ready.
I'm Jin Ju's father.
Hello.
I'd like to meet with you.
I'm sorry?
I said I want to meet.
Who's texting you this late?
We're all hoping you and Director Shin
get back together.
He deserves someone better than me.
Could you call the ER and ask
for the doctor on duty?
I'm on my way.
Do you really...
want to come here?
You can have all the dogs you want,
and we can live here, together.
It's cliché,
but I'm proposing.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)