Honestly…
Why do you even like me?
with such a lovable soul
Who wouldn’t fall in love?
They love you.
I’m sorry.
You work and take care of your family.
You’re all grown up, alright.
But did I take care of you properly?
Are you going back to being a mall owner?
But how will I see you after this?
You want to know Tim better?
Was it a good day or a bad day?
It’s been a good day.
Everything okay?
I dropped the hair dryer.
I see…
Why don’t you sit down?
I’ll dry your hair.
We’re done.
I’ll sleep on U’s couch.
Okay.
YOU KNOW WHO IS BAD
Hey, Tim?
Why didn’t you just stay at Pai’s?
I’d better not.
Too much chemistry.
Things could get out of hand.
Let’s get in.
But why does it matter
if something happens?
I can’t let that happen.
Our relationship is complicated enough as it is.
Complicated?
You love him.
He loves you.
It’s just that simple.
For Pai, love and second chances
are two different things.
So what, now you’re just
some guy chasing after him?
Pretty much.
Does that mean anyone
could shoot his shot with him?
Don’t jinx it!
I’m hopeless enough as it is
without any rivals.
What are you hoping for, though?
I want to marry him.
You do?
When I signed that marriage certificate,
I knew right away
we were meant to be partners,
in life and legally.
We’re meant to be family,
not just boyfriends.
But…
Can we really marry
the same person twice?
U.
U!
Yes?
Where’s your mind at?
What are you thinking?
And don’t lie.
Are you wracking your brain
for the new campaign?
Do you plan to please our manager?
Tell me your ideas.
I’m thinking about marriage.
Marriage…
A collaboration campaign with
the house decor department, huh?
What do you think about marriage?
I don’t think it’s going to work.
It’s too group-specific.
I don’t find that interesting myself.
Not at all?
For me, marriage has become unromantic.
It’s just a legal process.
If that’s the theme you’re thinking about,
count me out.
Right.
(You’re so over the top with this.)
(I’m only back as a head of department, not the CEO, you know.)
(That’s not mine.)
Oh?
Come in.
I knew you’d like it.
Don’t leave me on read, Pai.
Text me back!
Hey, U?
You at work?
Help me find out
who sent Pai a rose bouquet.
Red roses to welcome me back?
Why not?
They’re perfect for you.
That’s good enough for me.
U, North, I told you to
I promise I will knock next time.
Oh!
What a beautiful bouquet.
Did you give Pai that, Kuea?
Yes.
I don’t think people usually send red roses
for simple congratulations, you know?
This is weird.
It’s okay as long as you like it.
The flowers are so beautiful
I have to snap a shot for future reference.
That’s nice, actually.
Send me the photos, too.
Oh, sure thing.
Kuea, you jerk!
Where’s your hand?
Don’t tell me it’s on Pai’s waist!
What?
How did you get in here?
What are you doing here?
Traffic was bad.
I needed to pee.
Prem.
My house isn’t a damn gas station.
I’m already having a bad day, man.
What got you so worked up?
Look.
He has a new boyfriend?
No, he doesn’t!
But I’m sure Kuea is making his move.
I know he’s been eyeing Pai for a while.
If I was eyeing him, I’d have made
my move now as well.
Making a move right after a breakup
has an 80% success rate.
What good does that information do me?
It doesn’t help that I’m waiting for him.
What are you waiting for, though?
You did all that to him,
and expect him to make the first move?
I’m waiting for him to be ready.
Listen to me, you dummy.
He’s been in pain.
He has trust issues now.
The only person still has faith
in this relationship is you.
So you’re the one who has
to find a way to start over, not Pai.
What took you so long to tell me this?
Let me ask you something.
Would it be rude if I go to him now?
You have the audacity
to go back to Empire?
For real?
Ugh!
This is annoying!
It’d be nice to have my real estate
booth at your event.
I’ll find a spot for you.
Please come in.
U.
What’s the matter?
U and I just want to learn more about leasing.
Right.
Am I right, U?
Exactly.
That’s a good idea.
Go on.
I’ll continue.
If we’re successful with the booth,
I’m thinking I could have a shop here.
Hold on…
Selling houses in a mall?
Why not?
We even sell Rolls-Royce here.
But no one wants to buy a house anymore.
They probably prefer condominiums.
You know what I do when
I get asked this question?
Please.
Don’t do that again.
Let’s play a game with this tennis ball.
There’s only one rule: Don’t drop the ball.
What does that have to do with houses?
Let’s begin.
North.
Ugh.
See?
Throwing a tennis ball in a
limited space is frustrating.
But if there’s more space,
that changes everything.
North.
Kuea, catch!
You see how sometimes there’s
more joy in the space you’re in?
When it comes to space,
houses still beat condominiums.
Alright.
Okay.
I’ll take one.
I just sold one house.
Let’s call it a day.
But I must request that
Pai catch this last one.
No.
I don’t want to play.
Catch, Pai!
Pai!
Mr. Pai.
Where does it hurt?
I think I might have sprained my ankle.
Let me see.
Kuea, you don’t have to.
I’ll take care of him.
Let me down already.
I can walk to the sofa on my own.
No way.
I can’t risk you getting
any more injured, you know?
(Tim, Pai sprained his ankle.)
(Sorry. We were gonna have U carry him.)
(But I’d get so jealous…)
I can’t stand this anymore!
Excuse me, sir.
Visitors must exchange their badge.
I forgot my ID card.
Would a copy suffice?
It would not.
I must apologize.
But I’m…
Yes?
No. It’s…
Pai and I are
It’s alright.
He’s my guest.
I’m sorry, sir.
I’m new here.
I didn’t know.
It’s alright.
Thank you for letting me in.
And…
I’m sorry for everything.
I don’t accept baseless apologies
in random elevators.
Did you and Pai talk it out
about your relationship?
I want to ask Pai for a second chance.
I want to prove myself so he trusts me again.
You can prove your love to Pai.
But what will you do to regain my trust?
What matters most in your life?
My family.
Well, then, get us introduced.
And they’d better be your real family this time.
This is awful.
You need a new strategy
that doesn’t involve a tennis ball.
Come in.
Tim?
What are you doing here?
U texted me that you sprained your ankle.
I was worried.
Are you alright?
Don’t worry.
I already applied some ointment for him.
Are you alright?
Should we go to the doctor?
Let’s go.
Don’t be dramatic.
It was just a slip.
Pai.
It’s almost time for our dinner.
Where are you going?
We’ll be discussing work over dinner.
U and North will be there too.
Let me come, too.
I don’t think you should.
It’s for work, after all.
Bye.
Can you walk?
Let me support you.
Let go.
Pai, let me do it.
Shouldn’t I be taking care of you?
I can take care of him just fine.
Stay out of this.
You stay out of this.
Pai and I are working together today.
It’s you who’s intervening, Tim.
Enough!
Both of you can back off.
I can take care of myself.
Oh, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Mr. Pai, wait for me!
Pai, wait for me, too!
North.
Hey, hey.
Where do you think you’re going?
What?
You follow Pai right now.
Don’t let Kuea get anywhere near him.
More importantly, do not let Pai get drunk.
If he does, you carry him home.
Got it?
If you’re gonna be this fussy,
why not just wait outside his door?
Good idea.
Give it to me.
What?
Your keycard.
Are you for real?
Yeah!
Here.
Now go.
Good job, brother-in-law.
Go!
Run!
Of course!
When will your legal team send us
feedback on the contract again?
You shouldn’t be talking about that.
We’re off work now.
You said we were going to discuss work.
Alright.
I’ll get you the feedback by next week.
That’s it.
That’s all the work talk.
If you had a friend like that,
I’d be dying of jealousy.
Some friend, he is.
I can’t believe Pai can’t see it.
So… are you two still dating?
Yes.
Do you have a question, Kuea?
Just say it.
Your face is already saying half of it.
Well, then, I’ll be honest,
and I mean no offense.
How come you can still trust someone
who has lied to you?
If you don’t want to answer me, it’s alright.
It’s okay.
U has proven himself to me
that he really has changed.
Was it easy to forgive him?
Of course not.
Yes, he was wrong.
But he tried to fix his mistakes.
And I chose to forgive him.
If I want to be with him, there is
just no other way, is there?
Thank you.
If it were me and my boyfriend said that,
I’d have asked him
to marry me on the spot.
Right.
What time do you think it is?
Why are you home so late?
What are you doing here?
You told me to wait here.
How come North is so drunk?
Hold on.
He’s not drunk.
He ate too much so he’s in a food coma.
But Pai…
He’s dead drunk.
Kuea had to take him home.
I wonder what’s going on with them now…
You dumbass!
Why did you let him do that?
I had to take care of North!
You idiot!
You’re unreliable as hell, you know that?
I like you, Pai.
Will you give me a chance?
What?
You look like you never had a clue before.
I never did.
I’ve been in love with you
for more than 10 years, Pai.
Pai!
Pai.
You’re drunk.
Don’t make any decisions now.
I’m not that drunk.
You.
What kind of man are you
to confess your love and ask for a chance
when he’s in this state?
And what kind of man are you
to come banging at your ex’s door
in the middle of the night?
Don’t you think you’re making
Pai uncomfortable?
Pai would never be uncomfortable
because of me.
Tim.
You’re acting like a loser who
can’t accept the truth right now.
Kuea.
That’s enough.
I’ll talk to him.
Are you gonna be alright?
I’m okay.
You should go home.
Come on in.
Why are you doing this?
I’m sorry I crossed a line.
I don’t need your sarcasm right now.
I’m not being sarcastic.
I really did cross a line.
Kuea had a point.
I’m your ex.
I shouldn’t be here.
I don’t see you the way Kuea does.
Then how do you see me?
I never stopped loving you.
But each time I try to trust you again,
I get so scared.
About that…
I believe I might need to spend
my whole life to prove it to you.
But in the mean time,
can we get back together?
Tim, I think
I talked to your Grandpa today.
He told me to introduce my family to yours.
What?
Once you know all parts of me,
and you still want me,
we’ll get back together.
But if in the end you want to move on
to someone else,
or want to remain friends,
I won’t cross your boundaries again.
And I promise to be a good friend to you.
I won't make you worry.
Alright?
Hey.
What?
I want to propose to North.
Congrats.
I hope you get what you want.
Hello.
What are you looking for today?
I’m looking for wedding rings.
Of course.
That one’s perfect for North.
Can I take a look at this one?
Of course.
Excuse me.
Can I take a look at this one, too?
Of course.
I’ll show you both sets.
Please take your time.
You can try it on your boyfriend.
He’s not my boyfriend.
I’m the groomsman.
My apologies.
So your boyfriend isn’t here.
Do you know his ring size?
Oh…
Yes.
It’s…
This.
This is the size.
Please make it this big.
Of course. Please hang on.
Of course.
What about you, sir?
(If you still want me,)
(we’ll get back together.)
(But if in the end you want to move on to someone else,)
(I won’t cross your boundaries again.)
Come in.
Mr. Pai.
I need to talk to you.
Me?
Yes.
I…
I want to marry North.
If you still don’t trust me,
I’m more than happy to draft a contract
regarding North’s assets.
But North and I are more than
just boyfriends now.
What suddenly makes you
want to marry him again?
I was talking about marriages with Tim.
He said, to him, it’s starting his own family.
It’s being each other’s partner
in life and legally
And I couldn’t agree more.
I think North is mature enough
to make his own decision.
If North says yes,
I’ll talk to Grandpa for you.
You will?
From now on you can call me by my name.
Of course, Pai.
Thank you.
It’s okay.
Thank you so much, Pai.
I’m so happy.
Pai. Pai.
Here’s the plan, Pai.
North.
I’ve been looking for you.
I want to give you a house tour.
Maybe you can help me with the PR.
I see.
Sure.
I’ll call U.
No need.
We can go just the two of us.
I talked to your boss.
Let’s go.
Right.
Come on. Let’s get to work.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Here.
Let me help.
How tasteless.
It’s perfect for U and North, though.
What do you mean?
It’s basic but genuine.
KUEA
(North and I are almost there.)
Kuea is almost here with North.
You ready?
U!
North is almost here.
You done?
I’m almost done!
Hey.
Hurry up.
What?
You… You know of this house?
Don’t tell me you’re a scammer, too!
North.
Take a deep breath.
Now go inside.
Go on.
U.
North.
Will you give me another chance?
I promise to take good care of you.
We’ll… make it our real home.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
I will.
You said yes too quickly.
I spent hours making this
and you totally wasted it.
I love him, duh.
Guys, let’s take a photo.
Okay.
Alright.
Kuea, can you take a photo for us?
Wow.
Is this why I’m here?
Of course not.
Let’s take a photo.
Do your best, Kuea.
Alright. Let’s take that photo.
Let’s pose for a photo.
One, two, three.
Let’s take one video as well.
Let’s say “He said yes” together.
One, two, three.
He said yes!
I said yes!
I have a polaroid here.
Let’s take one.
Alright.
Okay.
Kuea, get in the photo.
Come on in right next to me.
Kuea, you’re out of the frame.
Sorry but can you crouch down?
Lower.
Let’s say “He said yes” again together.
One, two, three.
He said yes!
North, put that here.
Pure bailed out on us, huh?
And he was the one who brought all these.
Let me help.
No, you don’t.
Go back and celebrate with North.
And don’t forget to call Grandpa.
We’ll go to him to ask for his blessing officially soon.
Alright.
Thank you for giving me the loan
for the house again, Pai.
Hmm!
You call him by his name now?
He said a whole sentence,
and that’s the part you comprehend?
Thank you for today, Pai.
Bye.
Bye, Tim.
Goodbye.
Bye.
See you, Tim.
See ya.
Shall we go?
I’ll give you a ride.
No.
I need to talk to Kuea.
Kuea.
Hmm?
Wait outside.
I told you I like you.
I asked for a chance.
Do you have an answer for me now?
Where are you going?
You said you were going to
give me a ride home.
I thought you’d go home with Kuea.
You were holding his hands.
Why are you upset?
You said you’d still be a good friend to me
even if I chose someone else.
Fine!
Sure!
I’d be the perfect friend.
Let me just calm down a bit.
I turned him down.
He’s a friend.
I told him not to wait for me.
Because he and I can never
be anything else.
Does that mean there’s a chance for me?
You said you wanted an answer from me
after we meet your parents.
I’m alright with that.
I’ll give you an answer after that.
Of course.
Let’s go.
I’ll give you a ride.
Don’t touch me.
Sorry.
Hey.
U.
We still need it for the wedding.
I can’t wait to put a ring on your finger.
Thank you for asking me to marry you.
Thank you for saying yes.
What was Tim like as a child?
It was a tough time for our family when Tim was young.
He always acted like a hero, doing anything he could to help us out.
We had to tell him we were used to struggling
and that we needed him to only take good care of himself.
Look at him now.
He’s taking care of his boyfriend.
Did you know he’s a con artist who scams people to pay his debts?
Sir…
That…
He conned my grandson.
Grandpa.
What is this about, Tim?
I’m sorry.
It’s just as he said.
Tim.
Excuse me.
Papa.
Mama.
I just wanted our family to be back to how we were.
We used to be so happy.
But now…
You’re getting old
and still working for someone else,
laboring away your bodies,
and sleeping in a tiny flat.
I just can’t accept it.
Tim.
Do you think your mother and I would be happy
if the money you give us is dirty?
We would rather struggle
than have you do something like this.
I’m sorry.
I’ll quit.
Will you forgive me?
Tim.
You don’t have to do anything for us from now on.
Your mother and I really are okay.
Yes.
I’m so sorry.
I really must ask for your forgiveness, Mr. Soepohn.
We really don’t know how we’d make it up to you.
But we really are sorry.
Papa. Mama.
Please, get up.
Let’s not go to such extremes.
All this time, Tim has been proving to us that he’s really sorry for what he did
and that he loves my grandson.
But in all honesty, for me, he still has so much to prove.
But I won’t get in his way
if Pai wants to give him a chance.
Really, sir?
I’m willing to spend my whole life proving myself to you.
I’m sorry for what happened, Pai.
And I must thank you that you’re willing to give my son a chance.
Yes, ma’am.
You can’t control them, you can only raise them, indeed.
Just sell the house and pay him back with that money.
Yes.
Have a safe trip, you guys.
Let’s go.
You sent your Grandpa off?
Can I talk to you?
Of course.
So that was what my life was like before this.
I know it’s no excuse for me to hurt people.
I won’t lie to you again.
I don’t believe everything you said, Tim.
But…
I’ll give you another chance.
Let’s get back together.
You mean it?
Don’t change your mind.
Of course.
But we’ll take it slow.
Can I at least call you “baby” again?
Do what you want.
Baby.
I give you my blessing and hope your marriage is full of happiness.
Why do I want to get married?
I want to have a house
where I can take care of you in sickness and in health.
But more than anything, I just want us to completely belong to each other.
Will you marry me?