Chu.
I want to see His Majesty.
I know what you're going to say.
His Majesty is in a bad mood.
You'd better report on another day.
Ever since His Majesty
recovered from his illness,
he's been either searching everywhere
for Queen Chu's whereabouts
or drinking and making merry
in the hunting ground.
Military affairs have already
piled up like a mountain!
-Your Majesty.
Speak.
It has been 3 months
since Great Yong withdrew their troops.
Our spies there
brought a secret report today,
saying that Meilin Pass
may seem heavily guarded
and impregnable,
but in reality,
the troops from Xintai Pass
to the east have been moved west.
Now, Xintai Pass
is the most vulnerable place
in Great Yong.
The Yong Army previously
suffered heavy losses
in the Battle of Meilin Pass.
Meanwhile, our Great Yan
has ample rations,
enough to supply an eastward expedition
of 50,000 Yan soldiers.
Your Majesty,
I think we should attack Great Yong
before they have a chance
to catch their breath,
striking at their weakest point
and catching them off guard!
You.
Come here.
Your Majesty.
Look up.
What dance were you performing?
It is Great Yan's war dance.
It praises Great Yan's warriors
for fearing no strong enemy,
expanding territories,
and battling heaven and earth.
Expanding territories.
Battling heaven and earth.
Good!
You shall be rewarded!
Why did you stop me just now?
I rode hundreds of miles overnight
just to get an answer from His Majesty!
Why did you stop me?
Didn't you see His Majesty
was fixated on that dancer,
who looks a bit like Chu Qiao?
What good could possibly come of
discussing military affairs now?
Forget it.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 10]
Tea.
Your Majesty.
Why are you here?
I am here to serve you, Your Majesty.
Please do not mind my clumsiness.
Which tribe are you from?
Your Majesty,
I am from the Pale Tribe.
Pale Tribe.
Undress me.
The clothes and jewelry
you are wearing are very valuable.
Did Pale's old man reward you
to come and seduce me?
You must be joking, Your Majesty.
Elder Pale is my uncle.
When I was young,
I saw you at my uncle's mansion
and have admired you ever since.
Your Majesty...
Tell your self-righteous uncle,
if he tries to play smart next time,
you
won't walk out of here alive so easily.
Get out.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please calm down.
It is my dereliction of duty
to let that dancer...
What dancer?
She is Pale's old man's own niece!
They are so eager
to send their blood relatives
to my side.
What they want to climb onto
is not my bed,
but my throne!
Your Majesty,
forgive my bluntness.
These days,
there has been more restlessness
among the tribes.
Restlessness?
I know without you telling me.
All they're saying
is that the King of Great Yan
has no Queen and no heir.
So it is unknown
who Great Yan will belong to
in the future.
You overthink it, Your Majesty.
The elders wouldn't dare.
Wouldn't dare?
Chu.
In Great Yan,
only the one who can tame this black eagle
is qualified to be the King of Great Yan.
Come.
Chu,
be my Queen of Great Yan.
Who wants to be your Queen?
I don't care.
I didn't lie to you.
Really.
When my father comes to pick me up,
we will go back to Great Yan together.
There are rarely wars
or refugees in Great Yan.
Everyone has enough to eat.
Even slaves
can live as they wish.
Is what you said
true?
It's true, Chu.
When we get there,
no one will ever point a sword
at you again.
I can also take you
hunting horses in Huolei Plains
and soaking in hot springs
in Mount Huihui.
You will definitely like it there.
Please help me bring Chu back.
Bring her back
to make her the Queen of Great Yan.
[Border between Ximeng and Biantang]
One more city ahead
is the border of Biantang.
Once in Biantang,
you must keep a close eye on him.
If there is any sign of trouble,
report immediately.
There can be no mistakes.
Yes.
[Baze, Warrior of the Lingyue Clan]
Fu,
what's wrong?
Are you really scared?
He is not King Ximeng.
What?
I pay my respects
to you with Ximeng etiquette,
Your Majesty.
You are too polite, King Ximeng.
You must be tired from the journey.
We've prepared a state banquet
to welcome you, King Ximeng.
King Ximeng, you coming from afar
to ally with Biantang
is a joy for Biantang.
You are too polite, Your Majesty.
Although Ximeng is in a remote area,
we have long admired the prosperity
and peace of Biantang.
The purpose of my visit this time
is to see the elegance of Biantang.
Thank you for your hospitality.
King Ximeng,
on behalf of Biantang,
I offer you a toast.
To you, Your Majesty.
Wait.
According to the etiquette of Biantang,
wearing a mask at a state banquet
is disrespectful.
King Ximeng, you wear a mask
even when toasting.
Do you have no intention to drink
with His Majesty and me?
It's not that I don't want
to take off the mask,
but my face is strange
and terrifying.
Taking off the mask at a state banquet
would be inappropriate
and impolite.
When you met His Majesty just now,
you used the etiquette of Ximeng.
When toasting,
you are still unwilling
to take off your mask.
Are you so unwilling
to follow the etiquette of Biantang
because you look down on Biantang
as a small Central Plains country,
far less vast than Ximeng,
and thus show no respect
for His Majesty and me?
Why do you make things difficult
for me, Your Majesty?
If you don't want
to take off the mask yourself,
I will ask someone to help you.
You, go and take off his mask.
Useless thing.
How dare you disrespect King Ximeng!
Drag her out!
Beat her to death.
Your Majesty,
please spare my life! Please!
I know my mistake!
Your Majesty, please spare my life!
You go.
Your Majesty,
please spare my life! Please!
I know my mistake! I know my mistake!
I think those
who have always offended Biantang
and raped and plundered at the border,
although belonging to Ximeng,
must be some
undisciplined savage tribes.
A dignified King Ximeng
can't be such a cruel person.
He will never just watch
innocent people die.
Your Majesty,
I make bold to speak.
King Ximeng is of noble status.
It may be inappropriate for a maid
to take off his mask.
How about letting His Highness
see King Ximeng's true face in person?
What do you think?
Fu,
what are you doing?
I don't quite understand this.
What is your intention, Princess Fu?
King Ximeng came from afar
to make friends with Biantang.
He's probably not refusing
to remove his mask out of disrespect,
but because he
has some unspeakable difficulties.
The Crown Prince is the chosen one
and of noble status.
First, he can replace
the Emperor and the Empress
to see King Ximeng's true face.
Second, if only the Crown Prince goes,
it won't be impolite.
I guess King Ximeng
wouldn't refuse, right?
King Ximeng's face
was disfigured during the war,
so he wears a mask.
By pressing him like this,
are you intentionally
disrespecting our King
to humiliate him?
Since this
is about our diplomatic relations,
let's not let these trivial matters
ruin our harmony.
What do you say, King Ximeng?
Fu.
Ce,
what are you doing?
Mother, Father,
I...
I was afraid King Ximeng's terrifying face
would ruin everyone's good mood today,
so I wanted to share the burden for you.
Ce, since that's the case,
you can take a look
at King Ximeng's true face
on behalf of His Majesty and me.
Ghost!
Apologies for frightening you,
Your Highness.
Ghost!
Ce,
what exactly did you see?
Mother, Father,
I have seen King Ximeng's true face.
It is indeed as King Ximeng said.
His old wounds haven't healed,
so he shouldn't show his face.
So it is true.
His face is exceptionally
ugly and disfigured.
Absolutely terrifying.
Mother,
it's best not to let him
take off his mask.
Alright,
he has seen his face.
Let the banquet begin.
Your Majesty, please wait.
We have specially arranged
a performance for King Ximeng,
and it hasn't started yet.
These 3 Ximeng warriors
are all exceptionally strong,
yet they raped and pillaged
on our Biantang land.
I thought,
why not take the opportunity
of King Ximeng's visit today
to let our Biantang warriors
and Ximeng warriors
compete against each other?
Let the match begin.
You can't even hold your swords steadily.
If Ximeng people are like this,
how dare they call themselves warriors?
In my opinion,
they're nothing but cowards, not warriors!
I thought
Ximeng soldiers were so brave
and skilled in battle.
I didn't expect to see today
that they are so pathetic.
They are just like beasts.
These 3 warriors are obviously weak.
They look like
they haven't eaten for days.
This is simply bullying the weak!
Continue.
Your Majesty, please take our bodies
back to Ximeng.
My Queen,
King Ximeng came from afar.
Randomly picking some soldiers
to start a fight
is against our way of treating guests.
Your Majesty, you're absolutely right.
The Queen of Lingyue has a noble status.
If it's a match,
she shouldn't compete with soldiers.
Why not...
let Princess Fu do it?
Princess Fu is the daughter
of the Prince of Pingnan.
Not only is she a noble lady
of the mansion,
but she also
came from a family of generals.
She was raised and taught
by the Prince of Pingnan from childhood.
To compete against the Queen of Lingyue
is perfectly suitable.
Mother,
Fu is still injured.
-Don't worry.
-I'm afraid—
Princess Fu, like the Queen of Lingyue,
is of noble status.
The so-called match
is just a friendly spar.
They should stop before anyone gets hurt.
Don't you know martial arts?
Why didn't you fight back?
I came from a family of generals.
We only lead troops into battle,
not engage in reckless brawls.
Enough.
The Queen of Lingyue lacks manners
and injured your princess.
Please forgive us.
It's fine.
In a match,
accidents are inevitable.
We startled King Ximeng today.
It is truly Biantang's negligence.
I hope such a trivial matter
won't affect the friendship
between Ximeng and Biantang.
I came from thousands of miles away
to build good relations with Biantang.
Swords have no eyes.
Those plundering Ximeng warriors'
deaths are trivial,
but harming our diplomatic relations
would not be worth it.
King Ximeng, you're absolutely right.
You must be like me,
hoping for good relations
between our countries,
which is why you helped Princess Fu.
However, I feel that
Princess Fu and King Ximeng
have quite a deep connection.
King Ximeng
was unwilling to show his face,
yet the Crown Prince and Princess Fu
stepped in to help him out.
When Princess Fu
dueled with the Queen of Lingyue,
King Ximeng also lent a hand.
Why do I feel
that King Ximeng, the Crown Prince,
and Princess Fu
share some past connection
that we don't know about?
How could the Crown Prince
have a connection with King Ximeng?
Ximeng is a remote region,
and it's King Ximeng's first time
in Biantang.
This...
Is Her Majesty implying something?
Your Majesty, you must be joking.
King Ximeng is highly skilled
and very proud.
He won't even reveal his true face;
he is no ordinary person.
How could I
possibly establish a connection
with him so easily?
Naturally, I would like to befriend
King Ximeng as well.
But I'm afraid in King Ximeng's eyes,
no one is worthy of his trust.
Princess Fu, you're joking.
I felt like old friends with His Highness
and Princess Fu at first sight.
I have no intention of being arrogant.
Alright.
This has gone on long enough.
I am tired.
Since the Crown Prince
and King Ximeng feel like old friends,
then the Crown Prince will be in charge
of King Ximeng's itinerary in Biantang.
Crown Prince,
if you are unsure about anything,
ask Lord Wang from the Ministry of Rites.
How could Zhuge Yue become King Ximeng?
Qiao,
don't stay silent.
Are you hurt?
-I'll send the imperial physician to you.
-I'm fine.
I know you saw Zhuge Yue today,
and you are in a bad mood,
but it's okay.
Stop the carriage.
What's wrong?
I have things to do.
You go back first.
♪ We mock karma ♪
♪ For being unfair ♪
♪ Why is life ♪
♪ Often filled with regrets? ♪
Xing.
♪ My body scarred and worn ♪
Zhuge Yue.
♪ My soul lain bare and torn ♪
Ahead is the border of Great Yan.
♪ I pass along ♪
Let's part ways here.
♪ This fleeting world's chaotic song ♪
Xing.
♪ My heart holds quiet words ♪
Yan Xun is no longer who he used to be.
♪ Words I cannot speak at all ♪
Why do you still help him?
Yan Xun didn't choose to become like this.
♪ Hate and woe ♪
Who is the real culprit?
♪ All is out of my control ♪
This is the path I chose.
♪ The snow falls ♪
I won't look back.
I will go back to help him.
♪ With fate ♪
Wherever there are people in this world,
there will be power struggles
and people preying on each other.
♪ It will eventually ♪
The perfect world you want
♪ Fall before ♪
simply doesn't exist.
♪ The dawn ♪
Zhuge Yue,
♪ As a foreigner ♪
this is the difference between you and me.
You accept the rules of this world,
♪ Don't look, don't ask, and don't speak ♪
but I don't.
Since you chose this path yourself,
♪ Wander ♪
even if it leads through
a mountain of corpses and a sea of blood,
♪ With no resentment at all ♪
you will walk it alone.
But if one day,
you find you can no longer
take a step forward,
♪ The lock in my heart ♪
you know the way
♪ Put the memories ♪
♪ In the silence of the night ♪
back to Qingshan Manor.
♪ Wait ♪
♪ For the stars and moon
to part ways again ♪
♪ As a foreigner ♪
If you turn around one day,
♪ Don't look, don't ask, and don't speak ♪
I'll be
right behind you.
♪ Wander ♪
♪ With no resentment at all ♪
♪ Traveling alone ♪
♪ In a world ♪
♪ Where fate is unkind ♪
♪ Look ♪
♪ The mortal world has forgotten me ♪
♪ I wish ♪
♪ You'll forget me ♪
Oh no! The stable is on fire!
Hurry, put out the fire! Hurry!
Put it out!
Put out the fire!
Hurry! Get water!
Go fetch water!
What's going on?
Your Majesty,
it's nothing serious.
Just the haystacks in the stable
caught fire somehow.
I've ordered men to search the vicinity
to see if there's anything unusual.
No need.
The weather is dry,
making it easy for things to catch fire.
Everyone is tired today.
Let everyone rest early.
Yes.
The person who came today,
Princess Fu from the banquet,
is the woman you wanted
to use the Bone-Chilling Grass
to save.
I'm warning you.
Since you saved her,
don't cause any more trouble.
Although I can't kill you,
I can kill her.
Give it back to me!
This wood carving
is the token
of the Lingyue Clan, isn't it?
Five years ago,
King Ximeng led troops
to annex the Lingyue Tribe.
King Lingyue fought to the death
and was tortured to death by King Ximeng.
And the Queen of Lingyue
betrayed her own country
to follow King Ximeng.
She was cursed by her own people.
The Queen
is you, right?
Who told you?
A highly skilled
and arrogant woman
is actually willing
to be King Ximeng's slave.
Since I made a promise,
I will definitely fulfill it.
But if you dare to threaten me
with Chu Qiao again,
none of us will leave Tangjing alive.
I don't care about my own life.
And I care even less about your mission.
Wait.
[Tangjing, Biantang]
Little rabbits! Come take a look!
They're home-raised.
Little rabbits!
Yan Xun.
Chun'er.
Chun'er?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Chun'er.
Guess
what I brought back for you.
Today on the street,
I saw you staring at it,
so I guessed you might like it.
My mansion has always been quiet.
I figured you'd get bored
staying here all day.
So I went back to the archery stall
and won it for you,
hoping it could keep you company.
Chun'er!
Chun'er, what are you doing?
You said it yourself
this was a gift for me.
How I deal with it is my own business!
The rabbit!
It's yours, indeed.
But what did that rabbit do wrong?
Why were you so cruel to it?
Yes!
I am cruel and vicious.
Nobody likes me at all.
Everyone hates me!
So why do you still bother with me?
Just go!
Go away!
All you men are liars anyway.
Sooner or later,
you'll lie to me and bully me!
Chun'er.
I'm sorry.
You must have suffered
a lot of grievances.
But here with me,
I definitely won't let you suffer anymore.
Chun'er.
I will protect you
for the rest of my life.
You can't even kill me.
How can you kill them?
Your Majesty, please don't be sad.
Just punish me.
Based on my understanding of Zhuge Yue,
his visit to Biantang this time
is not simple.
Chu,
I miss you so much.
I pay my respects to you,
Princess Consort Helian.