We've been wandering around here
for so many days.
Have you found that Zhang—
what's his name again?
Have you found him?
Southeast,
southwest,
east market,
and west market.
Six central ministries, and 32 blocks.
We are here to find someone,
not to study the map of Tangjing.
Come and take a look.
Where is this place?
This
is the former site
of Qingluan Altar in Tangjing.
It is bordered by the Capital Prefecture
to the left
and the Empress's Furong Garden
to the right.
Nominally it has been abandoned
for a long time
and isn't even drawn on the map.
However, it is surrounded
by three watchtowers,
which are guarded day and night.
This is the secret residence of Director Zhang
that we are looking for.
We will act tonight.
[REBIRTH]
[Episode 12]
[Virtue of Zhang's Mansion]
I've searched the east wings.
No one was there.
He's not here. Let's go.
There are traps everywhere.
Let's go.
You're injured?
Who's there?
Go! I'll go lead them away!
The intruders are over there!
After them!
Yes!
The intruders are just ahead!
After them!
Search!
Who's there?
Greetings, Your Highness.
The people you're looking for
went that way.
Yes.
Let's go!
Xing?
Xing,
I know you have many questions,
and I should give you some explanation.
But I have my reasons not to.
Zhuge Yue,
I know you've been protecting me silently.
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't have nearly died
in the frozen lake.
Xing, it was not your fault.
I...
I thought we had a tacit understanding
and knew each other well.
We even went through
life and death together.
What exactly is it
that we can't face together?
I didn't expect you to still refuse
to tell me.
I could only help you this much today.
From now on,
I will tell myself
that the old Zhuge Yue sank into
the frozen lake forever
while trying to save me.
I'm sorry, Xing.
If I could still stand before you
properly,
I would definitely tell you everything.
The audience has arrived.
Let the show begin!
Today we will present you
"General Chu's Three Attacks
on Zhuge Yue".
The plot has ups and downs
and is deeply satisfying!
It's truly an excellent script.
Li Ce,
you're so lame.
Whether it's lame or not,
you have to watch it before you can judge.
The first strike
is for his eternally cold face.
He has a mouth,
but he never uses it properly.
Keeping a straight face all day,
as if the whole world owes him.
Qiao,
do you think that was a good strike?
Wait a minute.
There's a second strike.
This second strike
is for his arrogance
and superiority.
He's just an ordinary person
made of flesh and blood,
but he has to act like an immortal
descended to earth,
capable of handling all problems.
And the result?
He ended up covered in scars,
which made others feel bad for him.
The third strike
is for Zhuge Yue's self-righteousness.
He always claims
that everything he does
is to protect Qiao.
Without consulting anyone,
he has done many dangerous things
in the name of protection.
Does Qiao need your protection?
Qiao is the world-renowned General Chu.
She can protect herself.
How was it, Qiao?
Do you like the play?
If you do,
I've prepared Act Two.
"General Chu Meets
the Crown Prince of Biantang By Chance,
Fake Drama Turns Into Real Fate."
Li Ce.
I want to have a drink.
Drink?
Li Ce.
Let me ask you.
You said you liked Princess Fu
when you were young.
But besides Princess Fu,
you have so many female confidants
around you,
and a large group
of beauties in your mansion.
Are you sincere
to all of them?
Of course not.
With some,
I'm just playing along.
With others,
they are fair ladies.
As a gentleman,
I must woo them
and take my time to admire them.
It's like...
appreciating a painting
or a piece of music.
As for those I truly like,
there are very, very few.
I don't know why,
but my feelings for him...
are causing me pain.
True love is to feel
what the other person feels.
You can sense his happiness,
so naturally, you can also feel
the pain and struggle in his heart.
You would find joy because of him,
and naturally,
you would also feel pain because of him.
Li Ce,
have you ever truly loved someone?
It has already happened.
Qiao.
Li Ce!
Qiao!
Here you go.
Miss.
What would you like to buy, miss?
What did the lady
just buy from you?
She wasn't here to buy anything.
She left that handkerchief here for sale.
She is a regular customer.
Selling a handkerchief?
Yes.
That lady embroiders a handkerchief
every month
and brings it here to sell.
And every time,
it's sold
within 1 hour.
Do you know the person
who buys her handkerchiefs?
Of course I don't know them.
But it seems to always be the same lady,
wearing a veil and a bamboo hat,
wrapped up so tightly
that her face can't be seen clearly.
Is the handkerchief still here?
Yes.
I'll take this handkerchief.
Here you go.
Where is Wang Shi'er?
He's slacking off
and not practicing again, right?
Do you even need to ask?
He's definitely upstairs, tinkering with
his stupid contraptions again.
Wang Shi'er!
Beautiful, you are so ruthless.
I like it.
Your Highness!
Look at these new mechanisms I've set up.
Aren't they pretty good?
I was wrong! I was wrong!
Take a look at this first.
I feel there's something weird
about this handkerchief.
The stitching is uneven,
but it seems to follow a certain pattern.
I can't be sure either.
But I've seen something like this before
in an ancient tomb in the southern border.
Some tombs have symbols
of varying lengths inscribed
to record secret messages.
So you mean these stitches
could be some sort of code?
[Lyvwan Restaurant]
Crown Prince, you're here.
Lord Zhuge Ximeng,
what do you want from me?
I asked you here
to discuss a collaboration with you.
A collaboration?
What kind of collaboration?
I came to Biantang this time
to find someone—
Director Zhang Qingzhao
of the Ministry of Works.
You help me find him,
and I'll pay you.
Director Zhang is a key confidential official
in the Ministry of Works.
Why are you looking for him?
I need a craft diagram he has.
The techniques inside
can help Ximeng mine black gold.
If you're willing to cooperate with me,
after the deal is done,
you'll get 10 percent of the black gold
from this mine.
Ximeng has a black gold mine?
But Director Zhang
is a pillar of Biantang.
For nearly 40 years,
he's been responsible
for all major casting
and metallurgy tasks
in Biantang, including
even military fortifications.
What could
a mere title-holding Crown Prince like me
possibly do to help you?
You're right.
You really can't help me with much.
What do you mean by that?
But first,
currently, as the Crown Prince,
you're responsible for my travels.
You're like a sticky plaster
I can't shake off.
So it's better to be frank with you.
I'm warning you, Zhuge Yue,
if you keep talking like this,
we're done here.
Second,
although you have no power or influence,
that's actually your strength.
Strength?
You are a puppet Crown Prince,
so you need
this 10 percent
of black gold more than anyone else.
Are you saying I'm short of money?
Who are you looking down on?
You are the Crown Prince of Biantang.
Without this 10 percent of the black gold,
you naturally
won't lack food and clothing.
But what if you have it?
Perhaps you could turn the tables.
You never know.
But why should I cooperate with you?
You are neither from Biantang,
nor from Ximeng.
Why should I believe you?
But who else can you trust except me?
Since you said
you only hold an empty title,
I believe that in Biantang,
you don't have many people you can trust.
In that case,
what does it matter whose side I'm on?
Zhuge Yue,
do you have a knife in your mouth?
Why are you speaking so harshly?
I just confessed my feelings
to Qiao last night and got rejected.
Now I'm pissed off because of you.
What terrible luck do I have?
Really?
I didn't know about this.
Sorry for what I said
that upset you.
I am truly sorry.
How about this?
As an apology,
after this is done, I'll ask King Ximeng
to give you an extra 10 percent
as compensation.
What do you think?
Zhuge Yue,
come on!
Please hide the smile on your face
before you apologize to me, okay?
Are you that happy
that I was rejected by Qiao?
[Chunxiao Theater]
Take care.
Your Highness,
please come out.
When did you notice me?
During the day at the market,
I saw you buy my handkerchief.
On my way here just now,
I sensed someone following me,
so I guessed it was you.
So you admit that the handkerchief
is a tool for you
and the women in this theater
to pass messages?
Yes.
It's hard for us to meet usually,
so we've been using this method
to communicate.
Who are you?
You have already seen Rou.
I can't hide it from you anymore.
I was once a noble lady in Biantang.
Twenty years ago,
my father was involved
in the succession struggle
between the current emperor
and his eldest brother,
Crown Prince Maocheng.
He was eventually implicated,
and all my family members were executed.
I was sold as a slave.
Rou went through the same thing as I did.
She also became a slave because of
the palace coup at Xuri Palace.
That's when we met.
At first,
Rou and I
were sold to a brothel as slaves.
We only did the lowest kind of work,
didn't have enough to eat,
and we weren't even allowed
to serve customers.
In order to keep us alive,
I stole
and was beaten.
Later,
a customer took a liking to Rou,
which is how
she entered a theater to perform.
And I
did everything I could,
became a high-ranking servant
who could serve tea,
and was eventually bought and sent
into the Crown Prince's Mansion,
where I gained the Crown Prince's favor.
Over the years,
I've been using my looks to please men,
just to earn enough
to keep Rou and me alive.
The handkerchief you bought
is how Rou and I secretly communicate.
The code hidden in the stitches
is a form of women's script
that Rou and I use
to convey our feelings to each other.
And the package I just gave her
contained jewelry I secretly took
from the Crown Prince's Mansion
to support her.
Does Li Ce know
all of this?
Your Highness,
I have no intention of harming him.
His Highness is a good man.
I will do my best to serve him.
But if our backgrounds
are ever discovered,
I'm afraid even His Highness
wouldn't be able to protect us.
You've been following me all the way.
Why did you go and see
the Crown Prince of Biantang?
I need him.
What can someone like him even do?
I've looked into Director Zhang.
He is extremely cautious
and has more than one residence
here in Tangjing,
and his whereabouts are highly secret.
He is not greedy for money, women,
or fame.
He either stays indoors all day
or is always heavily guarded.
To find him,
I need someone in Biantang
who can move around freely.
So you told him
everything?
How dare you ruin our plan?
Don't resort to violence so easily.
Also,
don't follow me again.
[Fuhe Pavilion]
Qiao,
you came just in time.
I encountered something yesterday.
-I want to discuss it with you.
-Li Ce.
I also have something to discuss with you.
It's about Lady Ziming.
Ziming?
What happened to her?
Lady Ziming has a close friend
named Rou.
Do you know that?
Here, enjoy.
If it's the head, I'll send her away;
if it's the tail, I won't.
That doesn't count. One more time.
You said yesterday
you would go back and think about it.
How's the thinking going?
Thinking what?
I forgot.
I had a more important thing
to think about yesterday,
so I had no time for that.
What was it?
Since it's important,
I naturally can't tell just anyone
so easily.
Well, Zhuge Yue.
we've known each other for a while now.
We can be considered good brothers.
Let me ask you something.
You must answer truthfully.
What do you think of me?
Wait.
I'm handsome, suave,
elegant, and talented—
there's no need
to mention those qualities.
I mean,
do I have any
imperfections?
For example...
You talk too much.
I talk too much?
Then I'll stop talking.
Wait!
Why are we eating wontons here?
Here you go.
See that man?
He should be Director Zhang's butler.
Director Zhang
has more than one hidden residence.
A few days ago, I sneaked into one of
his secret residences in the north of the city.
I didn't find him,
but I found some clues
linked to this wonton stall.
If I'm not mistaken,
his second secret residence
should be nearby.
The wontons
were bought for him by his butler.
You came to see me for something?
What is it?
This matter
is quite serious.
Then say it quickly.
It's...
hard to explain in a few words.
Then tell me once you've figured out
how to explain it.
Qiao, don't go.
Don't be so impatient. Come on.
I'll tell you.
In short,
Ximeng has a lot of gold underground,
but they can't mine it, so they're getting
anxious but can't do anything about it.
Zhuge Yue came to me
to propose a cooperation.
He asked me to help him find Director Zhang
from the Ministry of Works
and his manufacturing diagram,
and he promised me
one-tenth of the profits afterward.
No,
two-tenths.
What are you talking about?
Princess, Your Highness.
Ziming requests an audience.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
Dear, what are you doing?
I've been concealing something
from you, Your Highness,
and I feel guilty about it.
Although I have failed your favor,
I beg you, Your Highness,
for the sake of the child in my womb,
do not send me away.
I am pregnant with your child.
Child?
Congratulations, Elder Helian.
The day before yesterday, His Majesty
announced the news
of making Lady Helian his concubine
to the world.
This has finally put us tribe elders
of Great Yan
at ease.
The future of Great Yan is now secured.
I always thought His Majesty
was reluctant to take a queen
because he still had feelings
for that slave.
Even the niece I sent to him
was sent back without hesitation.
I didn't expect that Helian Tribe,
though poor at riding and warfare,
to be so clever
when it comes to offering women.
Elder Pale, you must be joking.
Enough of this.
Come, come, let's drink.
Come on.
Come on, let's drink.
Good wine.
Elders,
since you are here to congratulate me
on becoming the Queen,
why did you start the banquet
without me?
Why are you here?
If I hadn't come,
how would I know
who are the Helian Tribe's friends
and who are our enemies?
And how could I speak well of you
before His Majesty?
The Helian Tribe
has truly become something.
We'll have to be more careful
with our words in the future.
Although the Helian Tribe has no troops,
it has women.
Elder Pale, you're right.
I used to think
only troops could strengthen a tribe.
But now I finally realize
that sometimes,
women can be very different
from each other.
If a woman is a princess consort,
she can be more valuable
than thousands of men
and thousands of fine cavalry.
You...
Princess Consort Helian,
you're absolutely right.
Although His Majesty
is wise and formidable,
he is also inscrutable.
We have long been troubled by the fact
that he has no one truly close to him.
Now that we have you,
we hope you will look after us,
Princess Consort Helian.
You're too kind.
Although His Majesty favors me now,
the Helian Tribe is still weak.
I will still need your support.
You flatter us.
You've just been named Princess Consort.
You must have a lot of things
to deal with.
We will take our leave now.
Let's go.
Farewell.
Let's go!
I am the chief of the Helian Tribe.
Who allowed you to come here
and tell me what to do?
Helian Chuan,
listen carefully.
From now on, you are
the head of the family in name only.
In reality,
I am the Princess Consort of Great Yan.
You must always remember
that without me,
you are nothing but a coward
who sold your sister's body
for a few worthless horses.
Do it!
Kill me!
Then send my body to Yan Xun.
You loser.
Yesterday,
I wrote a letter to Director Zhang
in your name.
I bribed the stall owner
to put it in the food box,
and the butler has already taken it.
Let's wait here for a while.
Let's see if he's willing to come out
and meet us after he reads it.
Why did you use my name?
Be quiet.
Don't look for me.
The wontons have gone mushy.
Your method didn't work.
Something's wrong.
This is Xing's handwriting.
Stop looking.
Director Zhang is no longer here.
The Ministry of Works decided to build
a river channel yesterday.
He has moved to
the Manufacturing Bureau overnight.
If you want to find him,
I can help you.
But we want
an additional 10 percent profit.
This is risky.
I'm not helping you.
I'm helping Li Ce.
Besides,
I have the map
of the Manufacturing Bureau.
Qiao,
this is the outfit I specially bought
for tonight's operation.
Am I breathtakingly handsome
and unrivaled in the world?
Something like breaking into
the Manufacturing Bureau at night—
Zhuge Yue can handle it on his own.
You don't know martial arts.
If you go...
Qiao,
don't worry.
It's inconvenient
for Zhuge Yue to show up.
I must use my identity as the Crown Prince
to persuade Director Zhang to help.
Rest assured.
I've memorized the map
of the Manufacturing Bureau
drawn by Wang Shi'er.
Zhuge Yue will be fine with me.
Li Ce,
actually, you don't have to cooperate
with Zhuge Yue.
According to our plan,
we can build up our own power.
We don't need his 30 percent share
of the gold mine
to expand our power
and counter the Empress.
Qiao.
I said I'd take you back to Biantang
to recover,
but since you came back with me,
you've been living in constant danger
without a single peaceful day.
I've played the fool for so many years.
I said I wanted to regroup and start over,
but in the end,
I still have to rely on you
to fight my battles for me.
I feel very bad about it.
However,
I have always been a good man
who repays evil with kindness.
So you've always had someone else
in your heart
and treated me roughly,
but it doesn't matter.
I've already left a way out for you.
Inside here are over 50
shop deeds from various cities
across Biantang and Great Yong,
along with thousands of mu
of fertile farmland.
If anything happens to me this time,
go to the pawnshop, get the money,
and leave Biantang.
You're getting physical again!
Jinx.
Strange.
Where is that
"Water Conservancy"?
Who are you?
Your Highness.
It's not your first day working here.
Don't you know the Crown Prince wants
Honghe fish?
Of course I know.
But Honghe fish is rare
and only sold in the West Market.
I usually go early in the morning
to get the fresh ones.
But unfortunately,
I was a quarter of an hour late today.
The best Honghe fish
was sent to the Zhan's Manor.
Honghe fish?
Sister,
this is Honghe fish.
It's very rare.
Your Highness.
Are you saying
Lord Zhan also likes Honghe fish?
Yes, Your Highness.
It's said that, apart from me,
the only regular customer
of the shop selling Honghe fish
in the West Market
is Zhan's Mansion.
Princess Fu.
Where is your lady?
Our lady?
She was sleeping here
just an hour ago.
Where did she go?
Take care.
Ziming...
works for the Empress!
[One day ago]
Catch them!
Your Majesty, are you feeling guilty
that you don't dare to see me?
If you can't get rid of him,
you are nothing but useless trash.
Get out! Get out, all of you!
If you like me, marry me
and make me your princess consort.
And bring a moment of peace
to the millions of people in Great Yan!
There are some things
I must do.