=The Moment I Met You=
=Episode 7=
Chu Yunchang, you're under arrest.
Father?
Wait, what is the meaning of this?
Buyu.
She is the Jade Squirrel,
Sect Leader of the Sacred Hand Sect.
What proof do you have?
Lady Thousand-Hands, Lin Xin'er,
identified her personally from prison.
I don't even know a Lin Xin'er.
Buyu.
I can vouch for this myself.
Lin Xin'er named her.
It's her.
Buyu.
Are you trying to protect Chu Yunchang?
Wushuang.
Did you actually
see the Jade Squirrel last night?
Are you absolutely sure it was Yunchang?
What are you implying?
Chang was injured saving my sister
and hasn't recovered yet.
Her wounds reopened today.
She nearly died.
My sister also said
that Chang was right here all night.
She didn't leave for a second.
If you really saw
the Jade Squirrel last night,
then it couldn't have been Chang.
Whether it was her or not,
we need to take her in for questioning.
Buyu.
Wushuang is just doing her job.
Take her.
Buyu...
It's okay. I'll go with them.
Buyu,
you can't visit her in prison.
Stay out of this!
Chang is only a suspect,
not a criminal.
Why should I recuse myself?
You...
Everyone knows about your relationship.
You have to recuse yourself.
Rong,
perfect timing.
You were watching Chang that night.
There's no way
she could have gone out.
I'm sorry, Buyu.
I was in Yunchang's room
the entire night,
but I did fall asleep for a while.
I can't rule out the possibility
that she's the Jade Squirrel.
Well said, Rong.
Last night, I told Rong
to look after Chu Yunchang,
but that was actually
a cover to monitor her.
Instead,
Rong slept like a log the entire night.
Just like that time
in the Three-Hand Sect dungeon,
she completely missed it
when Chu Yunchang moved against Li Wan.
Then, we had a run-in
with the Jade Squirrel
and managed to wound her.
Now, Chu Yunchang's old injury
just happens to flare up.
Do you really believe
this is all just a coincidence?
Do you have a solid chain of evidence?
Is Lin Xin'er's testimony
not enough for you?
I will find the proof I need
to show that Chang
isn't the Jade Squirrel.
And when I do, all of you
will owe her a formal apology.
(Honorable and incorruptible)
Mao Buyu!
You have completely lost your mind!
(Gate Bureau, Ministry of Justice)
(Ministry of Justice)
So, this is the Gate Bureau.
It's certainly impressive.
Fitting for a man of my status.
(Ministry of Justice)
This is a restricted area.
No unauthorized entry.
Unauthorized?
Look closely, pal.
I'm the future of this entire Bureau.
I don't care
if you're the sun god himself.
Why, you...
Hey, brother.
You're with the Gate Bureau, right?
We're all brothers here.
Here.
Take the boys out for some drinks.
What, not enough?
Wait, there's more.
Take it all.
Arrest him.
You!
What is this?
Trespassing on Gate Bureau grounds
and attempting to bribe a Constable.
Your action is highly suspicious.
Bribe?
This is the evidence.
Seize and interrogate him.
Yes, Constable Mao.
Do you have any idea who I am?
Move it.
Nice one, kid.
I'm going to remember your face.
(Gate Bureau, Ministry of Justice)
I am the Young Master...
Ouch, go each on me.
Buyu.
Squire Mei.
Your tea, sir.
You know as well as I do
that Chang is weak and helpless.
How could she possibly
be the Jade Squirrel?
Unless, of course,
we can prove the Queen Thief
of the South was lying.
That's the hard part.
Lin Xin'er has been caught.
She's naturally
taking down Chang with her.
Why do you say that?
Well, years ago,
(Xiangming Tea House)
our family had
business dealings with the Lins.
Everything seemed
perfectly fine at first,
but then we slowly realized
that they were actually
a family of thieves.
So, my father-in-law
reported them to the authorities.
Elder Chu was
perfectly justified in doing so.
That may be true, but...
But because of that,
he made an enemy of the Lin family.
If we could only prove
that Lin Xin'er is
framing Chang out of spite...
But unfortunately, there is no evidence.
Thanks for the insight.
As for the evidence,
I'll find a way.
I'm counting on you, Buyu.
Chang.
I'm not supposed to come here.
But, I had to sneak in tonight.
Quick.
Chang.
This place is cold and damp.
It's bad for recovery.
So I brought you an extra blanket.
Here.
Try this.
I'm fine, don't worry about me.
Sit.
I just don't understand
why Lin Xin'er
is going to such lengths to frame me.
It seems her ancestors
had a feud with your grandfather.
Don't worry. I'll keep digging.
Buyu.
You have to believe me.
I have never done anything
to harm an innocent soul.
I believe you.
Just focus on getting better.
Leave the rest to me.
It's just that...
there's one thing
I can't wrap my head around.
Why would Lin Xin'er name you
out of all people?
If this is just a personal vendetta,
she has to know
how easy it would be
to disprove a false accusation.
She can't be that silly.
How should I know?
Maybe...
Maybe she's just out of her mind.
Chang.
Do you know the Jade Squirrel?
Why would you ask me that?
I obviously don't believe you are her.
But if you, or your family,
were ever indebted to her,
and out of loyalty
you're covering for her...
Please, just tell me the truth.
Nothing of the sort.
My family has absolutely no connection
to the underworld.
Whether the Jade Squirrel is a hero
or a common criminal,
before the law,
there is no room for personal sentiment.
Chang,
you must tell me if you are
in a difficult position.
I will protect you, no matter what.
What if...
Hypothetically speaking, of course.
What if I really were the Jade Squirrel?
What would you do then?
I think...
you must have had your reasons.
Would you arrest me?
Yes.
Because I'm a constable.
But I would do
everything in my power to find evidence
to help reduce your sentence.
And would you still want to marry me?
I would.
No matter how long it takes,
I'd wait for you.
And what if I were sentenced to death?
Don't talk like that.
Trying to get away with it?
Keep dreaming.
Rest well.
I'll visit you again.
Come before nightfall.
It's so dark in here.
I'm scared.
Wait here.
♪Donning a mask to hide my heart♪
♪Playing a part with a hollow smile♪
♪Pitted against each other,
neither of us gives in♪
♪One is cold as ice,
the other is burning like fire♪
♪A love so deep,
yet destiny so fleeting♪
♪This fervor is buried deep within♪
♪I long for it so much,
I crave to return♪
♪To the moment we first met♪
♪Casting aside all obsession
just to be with you♪
Well?
It's not as dark now.
♪I can't untie the knot in your heart♪
Tonight, I'll borrow some light
from the moon
with this basin.
Don't worry.
I'll keep searching for evidence
to earn your freedom.
♪But I'll spend my life
keeping you safe♪
♪Lies and vows,
let them stay in the past♪
♪Let's return to when we first met♪
Tonight...
is a beautiful night.
You...
Help! Guards!
Is anyone there?
(Jailer, Jin Dian)
What's with the yelling?
It's the middle of the night!
Someone is here.
Right here!
There's no one.
She was here a moment ago!
She was right in this cell!
Shut up or get whipped!
But I...
Where is the Sacred Token?
How did you get in here?
Haven't you heard?
It's the Sacred Hand Sect's
Space-Shifting Arts.
What do you want?
If you don't want to talk,
that's fine.
But then I can't guarantee
this little vial
won't find its way into your eyes.
You...
You!
Guards! Someone, help!
Guards! Help me!
Someone's trying to kill me!
Have you lost your mind?
No, no!
It was her!
Who?
Her! It was her!
She just tried to kill me!
She was going to kill me!
It was her!
Get up.
What were you just doing?
Sleeping.
Crazy woman.
You're nothing but lies and nonsense!
No! Don't go!
I need to see Constable Mao!
Constable Mao!
I have to see Constable Mao!
I need to see him!
Help!
Constable Mao!
You're finally here!
Come here!
Constable Mao!
Listen to me!
Chu Yunchang
used the Space-Shifting Arts
to suddenly appear right here!
She was there, then she was over here!
Then, she talked to me.
She was threatening me!
She's going to kill me!
She had this little vial in her hand,
some kind of heart-piercing poison!
The moment I closed my eyes,
she tried to drop it in!
She wants me dead.
- She means it!
- Alright, alright.
I get it. Calm down.
Jin Dian.
Check her.
Yes.
She used the Space-Shifting Arts
to try and kill me!
She's really trying to kill me,
Constable Mao!
You have to believe me!
Please, believe me!
We checked it.
- It's just ordinary wound medicine.
- Right, right.
She's severely injured.
So, she was permitted to keep a vial.
This is the one!
She used this very vial
to poison my eyes and kill me!
Give it back to her.
No, Constable Mao!
You have to believe me!
Enough.
Believe me!
- You have to believe me!
- Move aside.
Don't lock it! Don't lock it!
You hurt my Auntie.
Do you really think
I'd let you off that easily?
You hurt my Auntie.
Do you really think
I'd let you off that easily?
Yu?
What are you doing here?
I heard you were
interrogating Lin Xin'er.
I wanted to see for myself.
This case involves Chu Yunchang.
You should stay out of this.
Don't worry.
I'm just here to observe,
not to interfere.
I trust your capabilities, Wushuang.
I know you won't let
an innocent person be harmed.
Naturally.
Since this concerns your fiancée,
I will investigate it thoroughly.
My Lady.
Lin Xin'er seems to have lost her mind.
She was perfectly fine
before she was caught.
Why the sudden breakdown
after being jailed?
If Lin Xin'er really is
mentally unstable,
then her testimony
won't hold any weight, will it?
Are you trying to shield Chu Yunchang?
How can I shield her
when there isn't a verdict?
Don't forget that you're a constable.
It's because I'm a constable
that I refuse
to let an innocent person be framed.
♪Grudges and regrets
are like strong wine♪
♪Drink it down and let it go♪
♪An empty cup for our love and hate♪
♪Tears blur a fate I can't control♪
♪Let's drink until dawn♪
♪Behind this mask, I'll never lie♪
♪Every reunion feels like the first♪
♪This hidden smile will never fade♪
♪One heart, standing by your side♪
♪To the ends of time♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪A silent prayer in my soul♪
♪Carrying my vow beneath the moon♪
♪Hoping we never drift apart again♪
♪On our way to forever♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪Just to be with you♪