=The Moment I Met You=
=Episode 3=
Weren't we going to ambush her?
Why the sudden change to poisoning?
We might not take her even in an ambush.
Poison is a safer bet.
What if I'm immune to all toxins?
(Qian, Li Wan's henchman)
Then, we'll have to do it the hard way.
Don't be afraid of her.
Just get it done!
Mark my words, Chu Yunchang,
this isn't over between us!
(Oh no, why is she back?)
(Whatever.)
(I'll just pretend I can't fight.)
Qian!
A one-hit knockout!
You really were hiding your strength.
Wait, did I really just do that?
You certainly did!
Who are you people?
What about her?
Forget it, just tie them both up!
Yunchang?
(Where did she go?)
Oh no, this is bad.
Buyu!
A girl named Zhizhi just came by.
The Three-Hand Sect
kidnapped Rong and Chang.
I also just got a tip.
Unusual activity
in the western outskirts.
Let's go.
I'll gather the men.
No time for that!
Why would those thieves kidnap you?
How should I know?
I'm a victim here, too.
Maybe they're trying to
extort money from my aunt and uncle.
Even now, you won't tell the truth?
That man called Li Wan
is the leader of the Three-Hand Sect.
What even is the Three-Hand Sect?
He came to your birthday!
Stop pretending.
That was only out of respect
for my aunt and uncle.
Chu Yunchang,
my brother
takes his feelings very seriously.
I really hope you aren't
just playing with him.
I take my feelings seriously, too.
As long as he stays true to me,
I would give my life for him.
And here I thought you were capable.
Turns out you're nothing special.
If I'd known,
I wouldn't have bothered Qian.
I could've saved
a thousand taels of silver.
He said your martial arts were weak.
You outnumbered us.
There's no honor in this.
Ha!
You're in no place to gloat.
Now that you're toast,
any last words?
What if my aunt and uncle find you?
You really think I'm afraid
of the King of Thieves?
The King of Thieves?
How is your uncle part of this?
Didn't I tell you to shut up?
Shut your mouth!
You shut your mouth!
Do you have any idea who I am?
She's right.
This has nothing to do with her.
Let her go.
Otherwise, you'll face
dire consequences.
Chu Yunchang,
don't get too cocky.
Right now,
you aren't the one in charge.
I am Mao Wenrong
of the Gate Bureau's Intel Corps.
If you're smart, you'll release me now.
You're from the Gate Bureau?
Perfect. Now I have evidence
of your collusion with them.
She's bluffing.
Nonsense.
Here's my badge!
You really are with the Bureau.
Then, I definitely can't let you leave.
You two are quite the beauties, too.
Don't blame me for what happens next.
Don't you dare!
Rong...
Don't get the wrong idea.
I still don't like you.
But as a constable,
I refuse to allow any crime
to be committed in my presence.
If you touch us,
the Gate Bureau will hunt you down.
Quite feisty, aren't you?
I know you want to save Rong,
but we could be outnumbered.
That doesn't matter now!
My sister and Chang were taken
quite a while ago.
We can't delay any longer!
Who's there?
Surround them!
This is Three-Hand Sect's territory!
Die!
Buyu, stay close to me.
I'll protect you!
Let one escape.
Don't you dare!
With such a beautiful little lady,
why wouldn't I dare?
Run while you can!
I'll kill you!
Sect Leader Li,
did you forget about me already?
Li Wan,
you betrayed the Martial Alliance,
then you defected to Lin Xin'er.
And now, you're preying
on innocent women.
Your crimes are heinous.
As the Grandmaster
of the Martial Alliance,
I shall purge the ranks!
You didn't need our help.
What happened to her?
She was knocked unconscious
trying to save me.
It seems he wanted to use you as a gift
to join the Southern Thieves.
Chang,
Mao Wenrong is a government official.
If she wakes up and talks,
how will you explain yourself?
She didn't see a thing.
Mao Wenrong might be difficult,
but she tried to protect me.
We can't hurt her.
We shouldn't stay here.
Let's head back.
I'll help carry her.
The Three-Hand Sect wouldn't
gather for no reason.
They might stir up more trouble.
I need to check it out.
No need.
When we came,
we already notified the Gate Bureau.
So Buyu is coming too?
Rong and I can't leave yet.
So Buyu really is with the Gate Bureau.
Why did you lie to me?
Now is not the time to settle that.
Let's head out first.
I didn't tell you
about Buyu's background
because I didn't want you to worry.
You guys go ahead.
He won't catch me.
What about you and her
being kidnapped for no reason?
Have you thought of
an explanation for Mao Buyu?
I'll say it's
because of your bad friends.
They saw how wealthy we are,
so they snatched me.
You little brat.
Jade Squirrel.
It really is you.
As Grandmaster of the martial world,
you instigated the Three-Hand Sect
to abduct my sister and fiancée.
What exactly are you after?
They aren't...
This won't stop me from arresting you.
The Jade Squirrel!
Gao Shun!
Stop the chase.
Saving my sister and Chang comes first.
She's injured. She won't get far.
Yunchang!
Yunchang! Chu Yunchang!
Help! Someone, help!
Quickly, help!
Help!
Chang!
Buyu!
Who did this?
It had to be Li Wan.
He tried to assault me.
Yunchang, she...
It's my fault.
Yunchang was injured while saving me.
She's badly hurt.
We must get her a doctor now.
(Rising Clouds)
Buyu,
it's all my fault.
As a constable,
I failed to protect Chu Yunchang.
Instead, she took such a heavy blow
just to save my life.
We have to do everything we can
to help her recover.
The best healer in the city
is already treating Chang.
She'll be fine.
Chang!
Mrs. Mei, Squire Mei.
How is she?
The doctor is still with her.
This is on you!
You did this to her!
Don't blame Buyu. It was me.
Yunchang was saving me...
Our Chang grew up
without a scratch on her.
But since the day she met you two,
it's been nothing but trouble.
Get out!
You aren't welcome here!
We are at fault.
But I'm not leaving
until she wakes up
and I know she's alright.
Buyu,
maybe we should head back for now.
We can return once they've calmed down.
I remember we have
some premium herbs at home.
Let's go fetch some for Ms. Chu.
We don't want your herbs!
Let them all in.
You're badly hurt.
It's best if you don't speak.
Come in.
Chang...
I'm fine.
Ms. Chu's abdominal injury is severe.
She's lost a lot of blood.
For the next few days,
you must watch her diet carefully
and ensure she gets plenty of rest.
She must not overexert herself.
The wound was quite deep.
Though I've managed to stitch it,
it will likely leave a scar.
Thank you, sir.
Zhizhi, go with the doctor
to get the herbs.
Follow me.
Are you still in pain?
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
Chang,
you've suffered a heavy injury.
You should save your strength.
Chang, your injuries are severe.
It's best that you rest now.
I'll fetch some precious herbs for you.
Yunchang,
I was wrong before.
I shouldn't have doubted you.
Focus on your recovery.
We'll come back to visit you soon.
Let's go.
Chang,
don't be a hero just because
you're a good fighter.
You nearly lost your life
because of Mao Buyu.
At least the outcome was good.
Rong accepts me now.
Well, I don't approve!
Their entire family is
with the Gate Bureau.
Besides, Mao Buyu is the reason
you're in this state.
I will never agree to this marriage.
Chang,
get some rest.
Your aunt is just upset.
Right?
What are you doing?
Let's go.
♪Grudges and regrets
are like strong wine♪
♪Drink it down and let it go♪
♪An empty cup for our love and hate♪
♪Tears blur a fate I can't control♪
♪Let's drink until dawn♪
♪Behind this mask, I'll never lie♪
♪Every reunion feels like the first♪
♪This hidden smile will never fade♪
♪One heart, standing by your side♪
♪To the ends of time♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪A silent prayer in my soul♪
♪Carrying my vow beneath the moon♪
♪Hoping we never drift apart again♪
♪On our way to forever♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪Just to be with you♪