=The Moment I Met You=
=Episode 6=
What is the meaning of this?
I am the Princess Consort Duan!
You are not her!
Who are you?
I am the Princess Consort Duan!
Don't listen to him!
He is the Imposter.
Calling me an imposter?
And what proof do you have?
The Prince has a red mole
behind his ear.
While you were in disguise,
did you include it?
His Highness does indeed
have a red mole.
I must ask Your Highness
to allow me to check.
How dare you!
Lady Thousand-Hands,
your reputation is well-earned.
But you still left a trail.
King of Thieves,
I'll give you that one.
They're both fakes!
Seize them!
King of Thieves!
I have the antidote.
Where is the Jade Squirrel?
Stop hiding like a coward!
Come and get it if you have the guts!
Nobody move!
Stay back!
Drop your weapons, or he dies!
Stop the fighting!
Help me! Save me!
It's the real Prince! He's the real one!
Put your swords down!
If His Highness is harmed,
it's all our heads!
Stand down!
Let's go!
Your Highness!
So much for the Sacred Hand Sect.
In the end, I'm the one who...
Lin Xin'er...
I have tolerated you,
yet you keep pushing your luck.
You show no regard
for the Martial Alliance.
A sneak attack?
Still better than your plot
against my aunt.
Enough talk. Hand over the antidote!
Watch out!
The greatest female constable,
Luo Wushuang.
Arrest them!
Luo Wushuang,
I did you a favor.
Let me go this time.
Take her in!
Jade Squirrel,
don't move.
I can tell you're not an evildoer.
No matter who you are,
come with me to the Bureau.
If you are willing
to turn over a new leaf,
perhaps I can...
Spare my life?
I doubt
a lowly constable is in any position
to make that call.
You broke the law.
You must face the consequences.
You live in the light.
How could you possibly understand
our lives in the shadows?
Buyu!
There's the Jade Squirrel!
Catch her!
Mao Buyu!
You're a constable!
You actually let her slip away!
After her!
Understood!
(It's daybreak.)
(The crisis has passed.)
Yunchang,
you should get some rest now.
I'll take my leave.
(Peace and Harmony)
Buyu? Wushuang?
What are you two doing here?
Rong?
You were here the whole time?
That's right.
You told me I should
look after Yunchang to repay her.
Rong,
are you certain you spent the night here
guarding Yunchang?
Of course.
It was Wushuang
who gave me the idea.
As thoughtful as ever.
But we were supposed
to be hunting the Jade Squirrel.
Why come to Chang's home?
You two kept mentioning Ms. Chu.
I was just curious
to see for myself.
Chang is injured.
She is still weak.
If you really want to visit her,
please wait a few days.
Sorry, I was inconsiderate.
(Was my suspicion misplaced?)
Sorry for the intrusion.
I'll take my leave as well, Buyu.
Why are you sweating so much?
Chang,
you're burning up.
Your wound has reopened!
I'll get the healer now.
No.
Auntie and Uncle will only worry.
We can't just ignore this injury.
I'm fine.
Where do we keep the bandages?
Wushuang.
Resorting to torture
before an interrogation...
is against protocol.
Uncle.
With vermin like this,
there's no need for rules.
Who is the Jade Squirrel?
Still won't talk?
It would be such a pity
for your pretty face to be ruined.
What a waste.
Would you really let me go
if I told you?
After falling into the hands
of Gate Bureau constables,
I don't expect to leave alive.
If you have the guts, kill me.
Go on!
I always prefer the tough ones.
It makes the interrogation
much more entertaining.
Chang...
I'll change your dressing now.
This might hurt.
Bear with me.
You know,
you are a woman, after all.
Pressing a branding iron
into that lovely face
is a bit too barbaric.
How about we try "The Scouring" instead?
Scouring?
It's simple. You take a basin of water,
boiled until it can melt flesh
right off the bone.
Then, you pour it over the body,
layer after layer.
Once the skin is
sufficiently softened,
you take this steel comb
to rake it across the body
with everything you've got.
Strip by strip...
But don't you worry.
"The Scouring" is actually
one of the mildest techniques
we have at the Gate Bureau.
It certainly won't kill you.
In fact, you'll be able to watch
as your own flesh
is peeled away,
piece
by piece.
Luo Wushuang!
You're a psychopath!
Just kill me!
Kill me now!
I'm giving you one last chance.
Either you talk now,
or you'll never speak again.
I...
No...
I have plenty of other games in mind.
Care to give them a try?
The Jade Squirrel
is Chu Yunchang.
♪Grudges and regrets
are like strong wine♪
♪Drink it down and let it go♪
♪An empty cup for our love and hate♪
♪Tears blur a fate I can't control♪
♪Let's drink until dawn♪
♪Behind this mask, I'll never lie♪
♪Every reunion feels like the first♪
♪This hidden smile will never fade♪
♪One heart, standing by your side♪
♪To the ends of time♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪A silent prayer in my soul♪
♪Carrying my vow beneath the moon♪
♪Hoping we never drift apart again♪
♪On our way to forever♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪Just to be with you♪