=The Moment I Met You=
=Episode 4=
Young Master Luo,
you're a man of status.
Why would you go to the Gate Bureau
to be a lowly constable?
Wouldn't it be better
to enjoy yourself
in this den of pleasure?
That's where you're wrong.
(Luo Wuxia, son of the Luo family)
As the only male heir of the Luo family,
I was destined
to be the world's greatest constable.
What would a lady like you know?
But I recall you don't
know any martial arts, Master Luo.
Money is all I need, isn't it?
Is there anything
that money can't solve?
If it can't be solved,
it just means you didn't pay enough.
(Hu Lie, the Black Twister)
What now?
Robbing me?
Fine.
You can take everything in the back.
But listen up.
You can take the money,
but do not delay me
from reporting to the Gate Bureau.
The Gate Bureau?
I hate constables the most.
Since you're a lackey
of the Gate Bureau,
you're meeting your end today!
Take him!
How dare you!
Do you know who I am?
Who my sister is?
Who my grandfather is?
He is the Commissioner...
Get down from there!
of the Bureau!
(Black Gale Abode)
(Wanted Poster)
(Honor as Vast as the Heavens)
(Luo Wushuang,
Deputy of the Gate Bureau)
So, you are the Black Twister.
Who are you?
Since the 10th year of Wanli,
you have ruled Black Gale Abode,
robbing countless merchants.
You hijacked official silver three times
and abducted twenty-one women.
Sister!
With 133 lives on your hands,
do you plead guilty?
Since you know my record so well,
you still dare to come here alone?
Aren't you afraid
of being eaten alive here?
Who is the lamb and who is the tiger?
That remains to be seen.
Kill her!
(Honor as Vast as the Heavens)
(Wanted Poster)
Luo Wushuang, Deputy
of the Gate Bureau's Field Corps,
reporting back to headquarters.
(Commissioner Luo Shixun)
My respects, Commissioner.
Shuang, you're back.
Grandfather.
You led the team that rescued Wuxia
and wiped out Black Gale Abode.
The Personnel Corps has
decided to commend you.
You've been promoted by three ranks.
Thank you, Commissioner.
Where is Wuxia?
Did he not return with you?
You'll have to wait for him.
He said that riding was too tiring,
so he insisted on
coming back by carriage.
It'll be a few more days.
Grandfather,
why did you
summon me back?
A private matter.
A private matter?
What is it?
I've arranged a blind date for you.
A blind date?
Dad, you know that Chang is
the only one I want to marry.
And yet...
Just listen to who it is
before you make a decision.
I don't care.
Even if she were the princess herself,
I wouldn't be interested.
It's Wushuang.
Who?
Luo Wushuang.
Don't worry, Chang.
I won't let you down.
What's wrong?
Are you taking back
the gift you gave me?
I never said I was taking it back.
I was just worried it'd be uncomfortable
while you were trying to sleep.
This is my "painkiller."
I need to hold on to it.
Chang, I'm so sorry.
My family did this to you.
I'm the one who should be saying sorry.
If my uncle hadn't offended
the wrong people in business,
your sister and I
wouldn't have been kidnapped.
Lately,
I've been thinking about us.
I believe that
for two people to be together,
sincerity comes first.
There shouldn't be secrets between us.
So...
Buyu, I...
Chang, you're right.
There should be
no secrets in a relationship.
That's why I need to apologize.
I need to be honest with you.
I...
Tell me.
My father is trying to set me up
with Luo Wushuang.
Who is that?
She's our Commissioner's granddaughter.
But please, don't worry.
Wushuang and I have been
like siblings since we were kids.
Besides, she's incredibly proud.
There's no way
she'd ever be interested in me.
Trust me.
I'll make sure to settle this
and explain everything to her.
Otherwise, my dad will keep meddling.
Is this what you wanted to tell me?
Don't get the wrong idea.
You're the only one in my heart.
You silly man.
You've told me the truth,
so how could I misunderstand?
You really are the best.
All right, Chang.
You're recovering.
You need to rest.
Come now.
Get some sleep.
I'll stay right here with you.
Stop!
(Lady Thousand-Hands, Lin Xin'er)
Fellow traveler, state your business.
Leave the cart, and you live.
Lady,
this belongs to the Sihai Escort.
Queen Thief of the South,
Lady Thousand-Hands!
Move out.
To the Capital.
It's time to meet the leader
of the Martial Alliance...
The Sacred Hand Sect.
Waiter! Bring some wine!
Coming right up!
Buyu,
do you know why
we are meeting today?
I heard our elders
wanted to set us up.
They certainly put
a lot of thought into this.
Shuang,
we're like brothers.
You couldn't possibly
be interested in me.
Waiter! Over here!
Coming!
If I weren't interested,
I wouldn't have come.
Then, stop drinking.
You should just eat.
Have some of this.
Buyu!
- Auntie!
- What a coincidence!
You're here too?
Buyu, who is this?
Buyu,
since when did your taste
become so poor?
How can you just sit here
chatting and eating with just any woman?
What did you say?
What did I say?
Did I say something?
I barely opened my mouth,
and you're already snapping.
How terrifying!
Little girl, listen up.
Being this nasty
will only scare the men away.
You... I...
Looking at it this way,
our Chang really is the best.
- She's refined and cultured.
- Chang...
And understanding too.
No wonder you're determined to marry her.
Wait, Shuang...
This is my fiancée's aunt.
She didn't mean it like that.
Oh, but I did.
I just can't stand seeing people
act all lonely and desperate.
Tell you what,
I'll have Auntie Yun arrange
dozens of men for you to meet.
That way, you won't have any time left
to cling to other people's fiancés!
Auntie!
Look, they are having a quarrel.
What's going on?
No idea.
Auntie, you should really eat something.
Just a few bites, Auntie.
Why are you still sitting here?
Go find Chang!
Yu.
Since you already have a fiancée,
why did you agree to meet me?
Wushuang,
this meeting
was my father's idea.
But I also wanted to make things clear.
There is no future for us.
If I have caused offense,
please forgive me.
Why don't you two finish the meal?
I'll take my leave.
I'm leaving too.
Buyu!
Until we meet again, lady!
Wushuang, take your time.
I've settled the bill.
Enjoy.
(Cuiyun Restaurant)
Scented sachets and pendants!
Not bad, Mao Buyu.
You went behind Chang's back
to have a blind date.
With a female Deputy, no less.
Auntie, you've got it all wrong.
I don't have
romantic feelings for Wushuang.
I can swear to it.
Drop the act.
If you're so brave,
go explain yourself to our Chang.
I told her about this.
I was just on my way to see her.
I'll take my leave now.
I'll only say one thing.
Chu Yunchang is my niece.
Keep your hands off her man.
And if I refuse?
Then, let me give you a little tip.
A lantern in a latrine
can bring death.
(Cuiyun Restaurant)
Nimbus Palm!
You're from the Sacred Hand Sect!
Let's go!
A Plum Blossom Dart...
The King of Thieves!
(What?)
(The Sacred Hand Sect
and the King of Thieves are)
(backing Chu Yunchang?)
♪Grudges and regrets
are like strong wine♪
♪Drink it down and let it go♪
♪An empty cup for our love and hate♪
♪Tears blur a fate I can't control♪
♪Let's drink until dawn♪
♪Behind this mask, I'll never lie♪
♪Every reunion feels like the first♪
♪This hidden smile will never fade♪
♪One heart, standing by your side♪
♪To the ends of time♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪A silent prayer in my soul♪
♪Carrying my vow beneath the moon♪
♪Hoping we never drift apart again♪
♪On our way to forever♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪Just to be with you♪