=The Moment I Met You=
=Episode 8=
The two of you are high-ranking
Gate Bureau constables.
Yet, you quarreled like street thugs
in front of your subordinates.
Unacceptable.
My apologies, sir.
Grandpa,
Mao Buyu is clearly losing his judgment.
He's protecting the Jade Squirrel.
Wushuang!
Until there's a conviction,
you can't accuse Chang.
I...
Enough.
Maintain your composure
during a major case.
I've filed the report.
In three days,
the Vice Minister himself
will interrogate Lin Xin'er.
The truth will come to light then.
The Vice Minister is taking over
just to get Lin Xin'er's testimony?
This...
Isn't that a bit excessive?
Grandpa is doing this
to close the case as soon as possible.
As long as the case remains open,
Ms. Chu has to stay behind bars.
In that case,
if there is no concrete evidence
proving Chang is the Jade Squirrel,
she should be released immediately.
And if the evidence is solid,
she should be beheaded in public.
Shuang!
Even if Lin Xin'er's word is suspect,
Chu Yunchang is still
the primary suspect.
Out of everyone she could have named,
why did she pick Chu Yunchang
as the Jade Squirrel?
A random accusation
or a personal grudge.
Either is possible.
You...
You just want to clear your lover's name.
Chang is innocent.
It's only right to prove her innocence.
But...
Buyu.
What matters right now
is finding the evidence.
The Gate Bureau will never
frame an innocent soul,
but we won't let
a criminal walk free either.
- Understood, Commissioner.
Buyu.
You're my right-hand man.
The most capable always
end up with the most work.
There's one more matter
I need you to handle.
Name it, Commissioner.
I'll give it my full attention.
Grandpa!
You have to help me!
One of your constables here
is a real piece of work.
He bullied me the moment I arrived!
He even threw me in a cell!
You have to make him pay!
It was him!
Right there!
That's the guy, Grandpa!
Wuxia, enough of your nonsense.
Buyu is the finest in our ranks.
Listen closely.
From now on, he is your master.
Me?
That's what I wanted
to discuss with you.
Buyu,
take Wuxia under your wing.
Train him hard and well.
Grandpa, no! Wait!
Fine by me,
dear disciple.
Stay away! Get away from me!
No!
Stop it!
It wasn't me! I didn't do it!
It wasn't me!
Please, just leave me alone!
You...
Stay away from me!
I'm begging you.
Please.
Just let me sleep, okay?
I'm begging you!
The Ministry of Justice is coming
to interrogate you tomorrow.
Our time is running out.
So, listen up.
You have two choices here.
One, you cooperate with me.
Or two,
a nightmare worse than death.
Fine.
Ask whatever you want.
But once you're done,
you have to let me get some sleep.
Deal.
First question.
Have you ever seen the Sacred Token?
The Sacred Token?
The Sacred Token...
I remember seeing it
with my master when I was a kid.
But I haven't seen it since.
The one I had was a replica
made by Jia Yizhen based on my memory.
Who is your master?
Master?
My master...
No, no!
I can't say!
I can't say anything!
I'm begging you...
I'm begging you, just let me go!
Please, just let me go!
Please!
How can your mental state be this weak?
You're far too fragile.
The alarm!
What are you all standing around for?
Catch the thief!
Guards! Someone!
My silver! It's all gone!
The Jade Squirrel struck again!
(Gate Bureau, Ministry of Justice)
Grandpa,
this has to be the work
of an accomplice.
Trust me on this.
Chu Yunchang is locked in a cell,
yet the Jade Squirrel is still
roaming free in the Capital.
Now that Lin Xin'er is incoherent,
the Vice Minister will see this
during the interrogation
and inevitably release Chu Yunchang.
This is clearly that woman's scheme.
The whole city is in a state of panic,
yet you're still fixated on
the woman behind bars.
How am I supposed to
explain this to my superiors?
Grandpa.
Please, give me one more chance.
Chu Yunchang.
You are the Jade Squirrel, aren't you?
Where is your proof?
Lin Xin'er identified you herself.
Fine.
If you can get her
to identify me one more time,
I'll confess.
Driving her mad
won't get you off the hook.
Today,
I'm getting a confession.
Are you going
to beat a confession out of me?
Whether you're innocent or not,
we'll find out after the beating.
Luo Wushuang,
do you know the consequences
of illegal torture?
And how will you look
after I'm done with you?
Do it!
Stop!
Don't you dare.
Not on my watch.
Buyu, don't get in my way.
Wushuang, do you realize
what you're doing?
You'll be stripped
of your rank for this!
If I deliver results,
nobody cares about the process.
Do it!
Mao Buyu!
Nobody moves!
Mao Buyu...
You're really doing this for her?
Wushuang, I'm saving you
from a mistake you can't fix.
If you actually cared about me,
you wouldn't be stopping me.
Do it!
Buyu!
- Yu!
- Buyu!
Buyu!
How could you be so reckless, Yu?
Reporting!
Constables.
What is it?
Vice Minister Zhou is here.
(Ministry of Justice)
(Vice Minister of Justice)
Bring in the prisoner Lin Xin'er
and the suspect Chu Yunchang.
Lin Xin'er.
You've been convicted of your crimes.
We won't discuss them further today.
You identified Chu Yunchang
as the Jade Squirrel, Sect Leader
of the Sacred Hand Sect.
Do you have any proof?
(Upholding the Law)
Vice Minister.
The prisoner killed herself.
How do you run this place?
You brought a lunatic
for me to interrogate?
Get her out of here.
Yes, sir.
(Upholding the Law)
Enough.
What other evidence is there
to charge Chu Yunchang
as the Jade Squirrel?
My Lord, I recently engaged
the Jade Squirrel in a duel.
She was suffering from an old injury,
which flared up during our fight.
Chu Yunchang's injury flared up
at that same time.
This is ironclad proof.
Vice Minister,
Yunchang's injury
was sustained from Li Wan
while saving my sister.
She is a fragile young woman.
After suffering a severe wound,
it's only natural
for it to flare up.
Summon Mao Wenrong.
Yes, sir.
Summon Mao Wenrong!
Vice Minister,
Chu Yunchang's injuries
were indeed sustained while saving me.
On the night at Prince Duan's Residence,
I was in Chu Yunchang's room
the entire time
watching over her.
I never personally saw her leave.
Rong!
Wushuang,
I am simply telling the truth,
without bias.
Even if I disliked Chu Yunchang
a hundred times over,
I would never frame her.
Hear the verdict.
The prisoner Lin Xin'er has
taken her own life.
Identify the body and close the case.
There is insufficient evidence
to convict Chu Yunchang.
She is released.
Luo Wushuang,
you dared to detain
a civilian without proof
and turned this case
into an absolute mess.
You are a reckless fool.
Report to the Personnel Corps.
You are demoted.
Vice Minister...
Hear me out.
Silence!
The Jade Squirrel has been
terrorizing the Capital for days,
robbing countess noble households.
You can't catch the real thief,
so you try to scapegoat a young girl?
Unbelievable!
I order you to catch
the real Jade Squirrel
within a hundred days.
If you try to fool me
with another fake...
Commissioner Luo,
you shall share the blame as well.
Understood.
Vice Minister Zhou!
Wuzhuang!
Chang.
Is your hand okay?
What is it?
Still feeling slighted?
It's my own fault for failing
to find concrete proof.
I'm the reason
Chu Yunchang walked away.
Here.
Have a taste.
I've called you impulsive.
You still haven't changed.
No wonder you were outsmarted again.
Grandpa...
Do you find Chu Yunchang
suspicious as well?
You have such a low tolerance
for this woman.
Is it because you truly doubt her,
or because of Mao Buyu?
It's both.
Professionally,
even if she isn't the Jade Squirrel,
she's definitely
with the Sacred Hand Sect.
She's a sworn enemy of our Gate Bureau.
And personally,
Grandpa, you know where I stand.
If I didn't have feelings for Mao Buyu,
I never would have agreed
to the blind date.
Buyu and I are of equal status.
A perfect match.
So I won't let some suspicious outsider
come and play him for a fool.
So, for duty and for love,
you refuse to let that Chu girl go.
Yes.
Good.
Then, you must be even more cautious.
If you truly believe Chu Yunchang
is the Jade Squirrel,
then you're dealing with
the world's newly-crowned Grandmaster.
Do you really think
she would let you catch her so easily?
I got too impatient this time.
It's just like the tea in your hand.
You won't know if it's truly
a good blend
until you've reached the very bottom.
Chang, what's the matter?
It's nothing.
Chang...
You definitely don't look "fine."
I had no idea Luo Wushuang
was so obsessed with you.
Is that what's bothering you?
That's not like you at all.
You're the only one who gets me.
Of course I do.
No matter what anyone says,
I will always believe in you.
It's not that I'm naive
or lack better judgment.
It's just...
I know my Chang
could never be a wicked villain.
So no matter what your reasons are,
you can tell me.
(Yunchang Flower Shop)
Does it hurt?
No.
It's just a scratch.
I'll say it one last time.
Even if you're protecting
the Jade Squirrel
because you're indebted to her,
I don't care.
We'll face the past together,
and we'll handle
whatever the future holds.
But...
you have to promise me one thing.
♪Grudges and regrets
are like strong wine♪
♪Drink it down and let it go♪
♪An empty cup for our love and hate♪
♪Tears blur a fate I can't control♪
♪Let's drink until dawn♪
♪Behind this mask, I'll never lie♪
♪Every reunion feels like the first♪
♪This hidden smile will never fade♪
♪One heart, standing by your side♪
♪To the ends of time♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪A silent prayer in my soul♪
♪Carrying my vow beneath the moon♪
♪Hoping we never drift apart again♪
♪On our way to forever♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪Just to be with you♪