=The Moment I Met You=
=Episode 1=
(Mao Buyu, Civet Lord)
Mao Buyu, the Civet Lord.
You've hidden among
the Embroidered Guard for years.
You've served His Majesty.
The land is plagued
by bandits as of late.
As a commander,
you are equally responsible.
You are ordered to go undercover at
the Ministry of Justice as a constable.
You are to capture the notorious
outlaw leader, the Jade Squirrel.
The thief's movements are unpredictable.
He is a major threat
to the Imperial Court.
The stakes are incredibly high.
Do not compromise your identity
as an Embroidered Guard.
I shall
obey the order.
(Mao's Residence)
Buyu!
Buyu...
Dad!
You little rascal!
You actually became an undercover
for the Gate Bureau!
(Mao Wenrong, Chief Constable, Intel Corps)
Buyu!
Director Liu.
(Director of Personnel, Liu Sanhuai)
Buyu.
Commissioner Luo signed the decree.
Starting today,
you are officially
a Gate Bureau's constable.
Buyu, I knew it.
I knew you wouldn't settle
for being a street loafer forever.
You're turning your life around.
The Mao legacy is in your hands now.
Look, Buyu.
Your constable uniform is right here.
Dad, Director Liu,
I just remembered
something very important.
I have to take care of it right now.
Dad, no...
Don't worry!
- I'll be back!
- Buyu!
- Where are you going?
- Buyu! Where you're going?
(Yunchang's Flower Shop)
(Chu Yunchang, The Jade Squirrel)
Chang!
Oh no.
I'm hurt.
Let me see it.
How bad is it?
Zhizhi!
Quick, get the medicine
before Buyu's scratch heals itself.
What brings you by?
I'm here to tell you some great news.
I'm officially a constable
for the Gate Bureau.
What?
From now on, no one will ever
mess with you again.
Chang,
I want you to meet my father.
Meet your father?
I want my father
to propose to your family.
(Zhizhi, the Poison Master)
I didn't know you were here, Mao.
It's nothing.
I should get going.
Be careful.
What is wrong with this world?
I can't believe Buyu
joined the Gate Bureau.
Sister,
I think you're actually pretty lucky.
You start off
by crossing paths
with such a dangerous man.
What are you going to do?
Are you still
going to meet his parents
this afternoon?
Maybe you should just skip it.
I must go.
Of course I'm going.
So what if he's a constable?
Nothing to be afraid of.
It's not like
his entire family is constables.
(Master Constables)
(No Thieves Under Heaven)
(I'm toast.)
(Buyu's entire family are
master constables.)
(I'm a mouse in a cat's den.)
Chang,
(Mao Jixian, Chief of the Probe Corps)
this is my father.
He's the Chief of the Probe Corps
at the Gate Bureau.
Greetings, Chief Mao.
This is my older sister,
Mao Wenrong from
the Gate Bureau's Intel Corps.
Hi, Sister Rong.
And this is my brother-in-law,
(Xu Anran, Chief Coroner)
Xu Anran, the Chief Coroner.
Ms. Chu.
Mind your own business.
Ms. Chu,
what exactly do you do for a living?
I run a flower shop.
It's a small business,
but it's enough to support me
and Buyu.
Ms. Chu,
the Mao family is
a lineage of constables.
Every member, man or woman,
serves the Gate Bureau.
Our teachings are clear.
If a Mao is to marry,
their spouse must also be
from the Gate Bureau.
Is that clear?
Dad, don't be so rigid.
Buyu,
as a member of the Gate Bureau,
I expect you to marry
a woman connected to the Bureau.
She can support you,
understand you, and assist you.
It will let you focus on solving cases
without any worries at home.
And what about love?
Love is something you grow into.
Look at my sister.
You forced her to marry  Anran.
I haven't seen
much love between them.
- Why you!
- You!
Darling,
have some fruit.
What makes you think
my husband and I aren't happy?
Honey, have some fruit.
Eat up!
Yes.
Sister,
give it a rest.
Your acting is terrible.
In any case, I will never approve
of you marrying a woman who isn't
with the Gate Bureau.
Over my dead body!
Dad, please.
Stop with the dark talk.
Chang, you wanted to see me?
Your family doesn't like me.
I don't want to hold you back.
We should break up.
Is that all the faith
you have in our love?
Even if we aren't together,
we can still be friends.
How can I just be friends with
the girl I fell for at first sight?
You need to cool off.
Chang,
I've fallen for you
since I first saw you.
I'm not letting you go.
And don't ever say that again.
You won't regret it?
No matter what happens,
you won't give up on me?
Never.
I already told my father.
As soon as I crack a major case,
I'm marrying you.
It's not that simple.
It used to be tough.
But now,
all I just need to
catch the notorious
Jade Squirrel.
The Jade Squirrel?
Let me tell you,
that squirrel is our ticket
to a life together.
I have to get to work.
I'll come find you in a few days.
(Fool.)
(The rodent you're hunting is me.)
(The Queen of Thieves, Chu Xiangling)
(The King of Thieves, Mei Guangzu)
The Nine-Dragon Lovers' Censer.
This is an heirloom from
the wealthiest family in the capital.
It's worth a massive fortune.
Now check this out.
The Dust-Repelling Pearl.
If you keep this on you,
you stay spotless
even after traveling a thousand li.
This is a real treasure.
Nice work, darling.
Auntie, Uncle.
Didn't we have a deal?
No more stealing.
I...
We weren't stealing.
We were just teaching a little lesson
to some petty thieves on our turf.
Exactly.
Save the excuses.
Stealing is stealing.
Well...
Fine, fine. It won't happen again.
Just this once, right?
Chang,
I heard
you met Mao Buyu's parents today.
What does
the Mao family do for a living?
I sent you two out on a job.
Why are you back so late?
What exactly does this Mao Buyu do?
Come on, tell us.
Tell us!
What's the big secret?
Dad,
Buyu is way too naive.
He hasn't even checked her background,
yet he's planning a life with her.
You can't let this stand.
Rong,
aren't we being a bit too harsh
on Chu Yunchang?
What are you saying?
We've only met her once.
We don't really know her,
yet we rejected her outright.
It's no wonder Buyu is pushing back.
If she's not with the Gate Bureau,
she has no place in this family.
That may be true,
but we need a solid reason
to actually convince Buyu.
(Yunchang's Flower Shop)
Is this the place?
Chief Mao!
What?
This is the flower shop
Buyu always visits.
Watch out, those flowers have thorns.
It's fine.
See? I told you so.
Today is your birthday.
Tell me what you want,
and it's yours.
Aren't you afraid of my thorns?
I wouldn't care
even if you were a cactus.
Dad? Sister?
What are you doing here?
We were just passing by.
We thought we'd stop in.
Chief Mao. Rong.
Please, come in.
So, this is your shop?
Rong,
if anything catches your eye,
it's on the house.
Nothing.
Yunchang,
who else is in your family?
Allow me to introduce everyone.
This is my aunt,
and this is my uncle.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, everyone.
Why didn't your aunt and uncle
use the front door?
It's a family tradition
to take the unusual path.
Besides, it's great exercise.
Two birds with one stone.
Exactly.
It's good for your health.
Yeah.
This is Buyu's father,
and this lady is his sister.
Chief Mao. Ms. Mao.
Chief Mao, what brings you here today?
Well, I...
Today is Chang's birthday,
so I brought my father
for a proper introduction.
I'm not marrying anyone but Chang.
My father was getting anxious,
so he wanted to meet you both.
I see. In that case,
please come in.
Wait, we haven't prepared anything yet.
Prepare what?
Is there something in this house
you're trying to hide?
No!
Most things here are best kept hidden.
(A family of constables
meets a family of fugitives.)
(Yunchang,)
(this is your ultimate test.)
(We can't let this whole thing
go down in flames today.)
♪Grudges and regrets
are like strong wine♪
♪Drink it down and let it go♪
♪An empty cup for our love and hate♪
♪Tears blur a fate I can't control♪
♪Let's drink until dawn♪
♪Behind this mask, I'll never lie♪
♪Every reunion feels like the first♪
♪This hidden smile will never fade♪
♪One heart, standing by your side♪
♪To the ends of time♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪A silent prayer in my soul♪
♪Carrying my vow beneath the moon♪
♪Hoping we never drift apart again♪
♪On our way to forever♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪Just to be with you♪