=The Moment I Met You=
=Episode 2=
(Chu's Residence)
This way, please.
Please, come in.
Master Mei,
your estate is quite grand.
Indeed.
Please.
After you.
(Where did Chang go?)
Your family practices martial arts?
Just for exercise.
To stay in shape.
This way, everyone.
Go on in.
- This way, please.
- Hurry, hurry!
Look over there.
Boy!
Hide these weights
and weapons in the cellar.
Zhizhi, cover your poison jars!
My aunt and uncle's rooms
are a disaster.
Lock the doors.
But...
Move it!
Got it.
What were you thinking,
inviting a constable over for dinner?
This is a mouse cooking for a cat.
You're making yourself their dinner.
Stop complaining.
Just get to work.
Over there, wipe it clean!
Yes!
Look over here.
Right, of course.
- This part is nice.
- This is our
side courtyard.
Why is there a saber here?
Hide it, quick!
(Honor in the Martial World)
We grow a lot of
plants and flowers here.
You see, Chief Mao?
Every now and then,
we come here to write poetry
or do some painting.
Yes, exactly.
Look, there's a birdcage too.
We used to have two birds,
but they flew away. What a shame.
They got away.
(Honor in the Martial World)
(Honor in the Mortal World)
Seriously?
Of course.
Our home is quite lovely, isn't it?
(Wealth and Abundance)
It feels like we walked in a circle.
You caught us.
The house is built in a loop.
The tea is already brewed inside.
Please, come in.
- This way.
- Wonderful.
Have some tea.
After you.
Chang,
I didn't have much time
to prepare a proper gift today.
(Wealth and Abundance)
So I want you to have this.
My mother gave this to me
before she passed.
I've always carried it with me.
She told me
that when I find the one I love,
I should give it to her.
Today, it's yours.
It's too precious.
(Wealth and Abundance)
I can't accept this.
My mother said
this is my daughter-in-law.
For her daughter-in-law.
(Wealth and Abundance)
Take it.
I'll accept it, then.
- Welcome, Chief Mao.
Please, come in.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Please, take a seat.
(Honor in the Mortal World)
Honor in the Mortal World?
This is our ancestral motto.
Squire Mei, your family is truly
one of integrity and open-mindedness.
You're too kind.
This birthday
really got our hearts racing.
(Chu Residence)
Chief Li Wan of the Three-Hand Sect,
here to pay his respects.
What's happening?
The Chief of the Three-Hand Sect
from West Capital Road
is here for the birthday?
He's just
making things worse?
Hurry up and get rid of him!
Get rid of him?
He's the leader of a sect.
I wouldn't dare just kick him out.
Why is Ms. Chu sitting
at the head of the table?
Today is Chang's birthday.
Of course she sits in the seat of honor.
Exactly.
Rong,
we are guests here.
Stop complaining.
On behalf of the Three-Hand Sect,
I wish Ms. Chu a grand 20th birthday!
That's not necessary.
You're a friend
of my aunt and uncle, after all.
Ms. Chu,
please accept
this pearl-studded shirt as a gift.
A pearl shirt?
I recall Princess Gaochang had one
that was reported stolen recently.
Well...
What a coincidence.
Looking at the luster,
it must be a knockoff, right?
Yes, yes!
Right.
If you don't care for that, Ms. Chu,
I also have this Jade Scepter.
This piece
was taken from the Prince Qin Tomb...
I mean, bought from
an antique shop next to the tomb.
With such lavish gifts,
just how much money
do you owe the family?
Thank you.
Zhizhi,
take this gentleman
to the side hall for some tea.
This way, please.
- After you.
- Let's go.
(Chu Residence)
I've played along long enough.
It's time you told us the truth.
What truth?
What do the Maos actually do?
They serve the Ministry of Revenue.
Ministry of Revenue?
Do you think we're fools?
With how rude and overbearing they are?
That doesn't look like it to me.
More like the Ministry of Justice.
Auntie...
Look at Mao Buyu.
Does he look smart to you?
Still won't give us the truth?
Fine.
But when you get burned later,
don't come crying to us.
Chang,
your aunt is right.
Our family is in a delicate spot.
Don't play with fire.
Miss,
Li Wan is back again.
Greetings, Sect Leader Chu.
Why are you back so soon?
Sect Leader,
something huge has happened.
A Queen Thief has arrived
from the South.
She's already wiped out
the Black Tiger Gang.
She's demanding
that we all submit to her.
She warned that if we don't,
our sect will be destroyed next.
Ever since the Sacred Hand Sect
lost the Sacred Token,
we aren't as powerful as we once were.
But we are still the leaders
of the Martial Alliance.
Who is this woman?
How can she be so arrogant?
Well...
The Alliance and the Southern Thieves
have always kept to their own sides.
This woman has openly crossed the line.
Sect Leader Chu,
please, stand up for us!
I'm staying out of this.
What?
Find help elsewhere.
What?!
Sect Leader! Sect Leader!
Sect Leader!
Guardians,
what is she thinking?
We are with the Martial Alliance!
An enemy is attacking us,
and she just walks away?
Does she want to see us wiped out?
She has her reasons.
Something is wrong with the Chus.
Don't you think their behavior today
proves they're hiding something from us?
Everyone has secrets.
Besides, we're not close enough for them
to tell us
every detail
of their lives.
Buyu,
that man who came to pay his respects
is definitely suspicious.
He didn't look like a merchant at all.
He looked like
someone from the martial world.
Dad is right.
I think that Li Wan
is the Three-Hand Sect leader
in my Intel Corps files.
Sister,
we need evidence before we talk.
Buyu,
their family are clearly compromised.
About this marriage...
You need to think twice.
Dad,
Chang is the one for me.
I'm only going to marry her.
I'm not changing my mind.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Is Chu Yunchang really
the only woman left on this earth?
Yes, she is.
Do you want your brother
to be a two-faced man?
You own marriage may be miserable,
but don't try to ruin mine.
That's uncalled for!
Rong!
How can you
speak to your sister like that?
Besides,
she and her husband
are perfectly in sync.
How are they unhappy?
How are they miserable?
Rong!
Chang.
Auntie.
The Sacred Hand Sect leads
the Martial Alliance.
As our Sect Leader,
how can you ignore the fact
that we are being bullied?
Besides, that female thief is likely here
because of
the Jade Squirrel.
That just proves my plan is working.
We lure out the Four Great Thieves
and recover the Sacred Token.
The Three-Hand Sect isn't worth
our protection.
What are you talking about?
Three months ago,
the dam in Tong County collapsed.
Countless families were displaced,
and thousands died.
Auntie,
you know this.
But what does that have to do with this?
From what I've found,
the Three-Hand Sect
violated our Alliance rules.
They stole the disaster relief supplies,
leaving the victims
with absolutely nothing.
Unacceptable!
To commit such a heartless act...
To break the Alliance rules,
act with such malice,
and harm innocent people,
they deserve to be wiped out!
You should have told me sooner.
I would have
taught them a lesson myself.
There's no need to alert them.
I actually want that female thief
to show herself soon.
This is infuriating!
If the Sacred Hand Sect
hadn't just stood by,
the Black Tiger and Green Dragon Gangs
wouldn't have fallen.
Fine.
If they won't help us when it matters,
then we'll just surrender.
But doing so
is too embarrassing.
We need to offer them a big gift.
What kind of gift?
The Grandmaster of the Martial Alliance,
Chu Yunchang.
Please come again!
Ms. Mao.
I'm the only one in the shop right now.
Good. I'm here for you.
Me?
I only know how to water flowers,
and nothing else.
I doubt that.
You don't just grow flowers.
You raise insects, too.
Venomous insects used for toxins, right?
Venomous insects?
We florists hate bugs
more than anything.
You shouldn't spread such rumors.
Fine. I'll buy a plant.
You want a plant?
We have many rare
and exotic species here.
What are you looking for?
I'll give you a tour.
No need. I'll choose for myself.
Ms. Mao...
Ms. Mao!
The backyard is off-limits!
See that?
I didn't even get to finish my warning.
Ms. Mao, I'm actually impressed.
In all my life,
that's the first time I've seen someone
punch a beehive with their bare hands.
You tricked me!
I didn't!
I tried to stop you, but I couldn't!
Look at that!
Her face has swollen up like a pillow!
Zhizhi, what's wrong with you?
Rong,
I have some top-tier herbal ointment.
It's perfect for bug bites.
Here.
Serves her right.
Rong, did you come here
for a specific reason?
I'll ask you straight.
Who exactly was that man
who came to see you on your birthday?
Didn't I already tell you?
He's a friend of my uncle's.
I don't buy it, Chu Yunchang.
Don't think your tracks are wiped clean.
I'm not someone to be trifled with.
I'll find evidence of your crimes.
There must be some misunderstanding.
(That man from the other day)
(must have been Li Wan,
leader of the Three-Hand Sect.)
(What exactly is his connection
to Chu Yunchang?)
Miss, would you like some rouge?
It'll work wonders for your skin.
Leave me alone!
What's your problem?
Chu Yunchang...
I'm not done with you!
♪Grudges and regrets
are like strong wine♪
♪Drink it down and let it go♪
♪An empty cup for our love and hate♪
♪Tears blur a fate I can't control♪
♪Let's drink until dawn♪
♪Behind this mask, I'll never lie♪
♪Every reunion feels like the first♪
♪This hidden smile will never fade♪
♪One heart, standing by your side♪
♪To the ends of time♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪A silent prayer in my soul♪
♪Carrying my vow beneath the moon♪
♪Hoping we never drift apart again♪
♪On our way to forever♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪Just to be with you♪