=The Moment I Met You=
=Episode 5=
(Ministry of Justice, Gate Bureau)
Commissioner.
Is Li Wan's autopsy report ready?
The palm strike
was clean and decisive.
A single, fatal blow.
It appears
that Chu Yunchang knows martial art.
I also suspect that Li Wan
wouldn't kidnap
a mere florist for no reason.
Every major event in the Capital
is linked to the Grandmaster
of the Martial Alliance.
It seems we won't have answers
until the Queen Thief of the South
finally makes her appearance.
Sect Leader!
What's the rush?
She is changing her bandages!
Speak!
Lady Thousand-Hands
is forcing her way here.
The two Guardians request your presence.
So, you are the Jade Squirrel.
What are you doing here?
I've come to issue a challenge.
A challenge?
I want a duel.
The winner
becomes the true
Grandmaster of the Martial Alliance.
Fine, you win.
You...
I've been looking
for an excuse to drop the title anyway.
If you want it,
I'll hand it over now.
Bye-bye.
Chu Yunchang!
You are far too arrogant!
Are you even being reasonable?
You came here to issue a challenge,
I forfeit, and you lost your temper?
You've left me no choice.
Why don't you take a look
(Northern Martial Alliance, Token)
at what this is?
(Token)
The Sacred Token!
(Northern Martial Alliance, Token)
You aren't the first person
to wave a fake Sacred Token around.
You think it's a fake?
Then, I'll leave it
at Red Leaf Villa for three days.
If you don't come for it,
I'll hand it over to the Gate Bureau.
When the Sacred Hand Sect's
greatest treasure
falls into the hands of the Bureau,
you'll become the laughingstock
of the martial world.
I'd love to see
how you'll show your face
as the Grandmaster
of this Alliance then.
Chang!
I think the token
in that image was real.
If she truly had the real Sacred Token,
she would've commanded the world.
Chang!
Quickly, get a healer!
No.
Lin Xin'er is still suspicious.
Her people must be
staking out the entrance.
I just need to lie down for a bit.
(A new lead
to the Sacred Token was revealed.)
(The Grandmaster is still recovering.)
(I'll scout Red Leaf Villa first.)
(Token)
(The Sacred Token really is here.)
Go.
Let's move.
Where is the antidote
for the Seven-Flower Toxin?
Since you refused my challenge,
I had to force your hand.
By the way,
where is Chu Yunchang?
Why isn't she coming out?
Is she scared?
To deal with you,
there's no need for the Grandmaster.
I am more than enough.
Hand over the antidote.
I've already placed it
in Prince Duan's Treasure Trove.
Pick another place.
I'll duel you.
I only duel Chu Yunchang.
Tell her that if she wants
to save Chu Xiangling's life,
she must get to the antidote before me,
by sunrise tomorrow.
Otherwise...
Chu Xiangling is as good as dead.
(Chu's Residence)
Sanbao?
Mistress.
Go send a message to the Gate Bureau.
Tell them the Jade Squirrel
is going to hit
Prince Duan's Residence tonight.
Understood.
Rong.
Our spies report
that the Jade Squirrel will hit
Prince Duan's Residence tonight.
There will be chaos in the Capital.
Haven't you been saying
how guilty you feel toward Ms. Chu?
Here's a perfect chance to repay her.
You mean...
Ms. Chu is just a young woman,
and she's still injured.
It's not safe for her
to guard that flower shop alone.
Why don't you rush over there
and stay by her side all night?
Think of it as settling your debt.
Wushuang,
thank you for letting me know.
I'll get changed
and head there.
Good.
(Tonight, I am definitely
catching the Jade Squirrel.)
Miss,
Mao Buyu's sister is here to see you.
Rong? Why are you here?
Don't move.
Yunchang, I'm sorry.
You were hurt because of me.
It's only right that I visit you.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine now.
That's good.
This is top-tier scar ointment.
I hope it helps with your recovery.
Thank you.
(Is Mao Wenrong up to something?)
(She'd better not tell Chang
about the plan)
(at Prince Duan's Residence.)
You've seen her.
She's clearly doing fine.
You can leave now.
I'm in no rush.
I'm staying here with you tonight.
Why?
No!
Zhizhi.
What is wrong with you?
You've been acting strange all evening.
She must have heard about
what's happening
at Prince Duan's Residence tonight.
What's wrong with it?
It's getting late.
We should turn in early,
don't you think?
Rong,
did something happen at the residence?
The Jade Squirrel made a bet
with Lady Thousand-Hands.
He declared he would raid
Prince Duan's Residence tonight.
The entire city is now under lockdown.
That's their business.
What does it have to do with my sister?
She's currently bedridden with an injury
and needs her rest.
You shouldn't disturb her.
Buyu is out on a mission.
He's worried about your safety.
So, I will be staying here tonight
to protect you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Well,
I really don't like
being watched while I sleep.
Perhaps
you should head back.
Exactly. You should leave.
Let my sister get some rest.
I'll just keep watch right beside you.
I won't make a sound.
Your safety is at stake, Yunchang.
Please, do not refuse.
I'm a bit tired
from the flower arranging earlier.
I want to sleep for a while.
Zhizhi.
Light the incense for me.
I want to sleep peacefully.
Right away.
(Prince Duan's Residence)
We will surround the place and wait
for the target.
Do not alert them.
Yu,
it's going to be hard
not to alert anyone this time.
Everyone, look sharp!
Show them the might
of the Embroidered Guard!
(Embroidered Guard, Official Zhuang)
Official Zhuang, I presume?
Look who we have here.
The Gate Bureau is hunting a thief.
Why is the Embroidered Guard here too?
His Highness Prince Duan
feared you lot were out of your depth.
He sent word to our Commander-in-Chief,
requesting that the Embroidered Guard
lead the operation.
Now that we've arrived,
you may clear out.
Not so fast.
Catching thieves
is the sole jurisdiction
of the Gate Bureau.
By surrounding the manor
with such a spectacle,
you're just alerting the target?
The thief will be ready.
I want them to know
who they're up against..
The Embroidered Guard
is holding the line here tonight.
If those thieves are truly suicidal,
let them try their luck.
Vice Commissioner.
His Highness asks that
you lead your squad inside
to secure the Prince
and Princess's chambers.
What about our orders?
Chief Constable Yue,
lead your team to the Treasure Trove.
With the Embroidered Guard on site,
I see no reason to rely
on the Gate Bureau.
They are dead weight.
Move.
Right this way.
(Treasure Trove)
Who goes there?
Stand down.
It's me.
- My respects, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
shouldn't you be
in the safe room?
(Prince Duan)
Because the Treasure Trove
weighs heavily on my mind.
These are imperial gifts.
I won't risk even a single scratch.
I need to verify the inventory myself.
But the thief
is targeting this chamber.
Inspecting it now
seems too risky.
Risky in what sense?
(Treasure Trove)
Your Highness.
This is Prince Duan's Residence.
The Prince's own home.
If His Highness wishes to inspect
his own treasures,
how is that wrong?
The Gate Bureau certainly
has a lot of bluster.
And quite a lot of nerve, too!
You dare command His Highness?
That's not what we're doing.
We simply fear a security breach.
What breach?
The Prince is checking his own property.
Where is the breach in that?
If a thief takes advantage
of this moment,
can you bear the responsibility?
Are you implying
that we are incompetent?
You...
After you, Your Highness.
Worthless fools.
This way, Your Highness.
Who's there?
(Consort Duan)
Your Highness?
What are you doing here?
I am checking
the treasures for the Prince.
Wait. Did anyone see
Her Highness enter the Treasure Trove?
We've been guarding the entrance.
No one has gone in or out.
Who are you, really?
What is the meaning of this?
I am Princess Consort Duan!
Imposter!
Who are you?
♪Grudges and regrets
are like strong wine♪
♪Drink it down and let it go♪
♪An empty cup for our love and hate♪
♪Tears blur a fate I can't control♪
♪Let's drink until dawn♪
♪Behind this mask, I'll never lie♪
♪Every reunion feels like the first♪
♪This hidden smile will never fade♪
♪One heart, standing by your side♪
♪To the ends of time♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪A silent prayer in my soul♪
♪Carrying my vow beneath the moon♪
♪Hoping we never drift apart again♪
♪On our way to forever♪
♪The moon traces your face♪
♪Draped in clouds, you fill my heart♪
♪To find you
and keep our promise forever♪
♪Just to be with you♪